<opt>
  <artist name="Beastie Boys">
    <album name="Check Your Head" year="1988">
      <song title="Jimmy James" track="1">People how you doing there's a new day dawning
For the earth mother it's a brand new morning
For such a long while there's been such a longing
But now the sun is shining let's roll back the awning

This is a type of kinda like a formal dedication
Giving out a shout for much inspiration
All I ever really want to do is get nice
Get loose and goof my little slice of life
Sendin' out love to all corners of the land
I jump up on the stage and take the mic
In my hand not playin' the roll just being who I am
And if you try to dis me I couldn't give a damn
'cause I'm rockin'

Bass from the back of my car feels soothing
Eight bazookas is what I'm using
I'm mike d and it's been proven
I love it when I see the party people get movin'
Strapped on the ear goggles and what did I see
But the music brought the people into harmony</song>
      <song title="Funky Boss" track="2">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Pass The Mic" track="3">If you can feel what I'm feeling then it's a musical masterpiece
If you can hear what I'm dealing with then that's cool at least
What's running through my mind comes through in my walk
True feelings are shown from the way that I talk
And this is me y'all, I M.C. y'all
My name is M.C.A. and I still do what i please
And now I'd like to introduce what's up?
I'll pass the mic to D. for a fist full of truth

The name is D. y'all and I don't play
And I can rock a block party 'til your hair turns grey
So, what you sayin'? I explode on site
I'm like jimmy walker I'm dynomite
And now I'd like to pass the mic
To adrock c'mon and do anything you like

I'm the A.D.R.O.C.K.
In the place with the bass I'm going all the way
I can't stop y'all tock tick y'all
And if you think that you're slick you'll catch a brick y'all
'cause I'm a turn it in and i'm a turn it out
But now I've got to pass the mic to yauch

Well on and on and on and on I can't stop y'all 'til the early morn'
So rock rock y'all tick tock y'all to the beat y'all
C'mon and rock y'all

I give thanks for inspiration it guides my mind along the way
A lot of people get jealous, they're talking about me
But that's just 'cause they haven't got a thing to say

Everybody's rapping like it's a commercial
Actin' like life is a big commercial
So this is what I've got to say to you all
Be true to yourself and you will never fall
And now I'd like to pass the mic to the a

So what's your name, yauch? my name is M.C.A.
I've been coming to where I am from the get go
Find that I can groove with the beat when i let go
So put your worries on hold
Get up and groove with the rhythm in your soul
And now I'd like to pass the mic
To my brother adrock c'mon and shine like a light

Yes yes y'all and yes yes y'all
I'm always on time never the less y'all
And that's right y'all, I shed light y'all
I've got no time in my life to get uptight y'all
So what you gonna say that I don't know already?
I'm like clyde and I'm rockin' steady
But time flies when you're having fun
So mike d that's me c'mon and get some

M.I.K.E. to the D.
You come and see me and you pay a fee
Do what I do professionally
To tell the truth I am exactly what i want to be
Now ad-rock huh? and M.C.A. yeh?
Let's rock this joint in the old school way

Well I'm on 'til the crack of dawn
Mowing down M.C.'s like I'm mowing a lawn
I go off like nothing can phase me
You think we'll ever meet stevie? one of these days, D.
But I can stand my ground and i am down
To wax an M.C. who acts like a clown
But for now, I'd like to ask you how
You like the feel of the bass in your face in the crowd</song>
      <song title="Gratitude" track="4">Good times gone and you missed them
What's gone wrong in your system
Things they bounce just like a spalding
What'd you think did you miss your calling
It's so free this kind of feeling
It's like life it's so appealing
When you've got so much to say
It's called gratitude, and rhat's right

Good times gone but you feed it
Hate's grown strong you feel you need it
Just one thing do you know
What you think that the world owes you
What's gonna set you free
Look inside and you'll see
When you've got so much to say
It's called gratitude, and that's right</song>
      <song title="Lighten Up" track="5">Lighten up shine like the sun</song>
      <song title="Finger Licken' Good" track="6">Finger licken, finger licken good y'all

So mike d what's up? yo yauch what's up?
Come on mike let's tear it up
Hear no evil see no evil talking no bullshit
So many damn people are so damn full of it
Keyboard money mark you know he's not having it
Just give him some wood and he'll build you a cabinet
I'm convinced that vince is ripping me off
I think it's his girdle that's tipping me off
Mike d's out back and he's growing onions
I've got bigger buns than my man paul bunyon's
I've been going nuts gettin' all cooped up
Fully hermitizing but now I'm getting souped up
It's time to turn the page to a brand new chapter
Setting my sights and you know what I'm after
I'll be in the paper the news with ernie ernesto
They'll even print my recipe for pasta with pesto
Now here's another special of the day
I've got more spice than the frugal gourmet

Well mike d what got for me
Show these good people what it means to be d
Well they call me mike d with the mad man style
I put the mic up to my lips and I can scream for a while
Created a sound at which many were shocked
I've got a million ideas that I ain't even rocked
I've got the light bulb flashing at the top of my head
Never wake up on the wrong side of the bed
You're an idea man not a yes man
With a point to make you're bound to take a stand
'cause I'm pete the puma minnie the moocher
Got every type of flavor that will suit ya
You know the bass is real fat because it's gotta be like that
A snare on the funky tin and a taste of the high hat

Yo yauch what's up? mike d what's up?
Come on yauch, let's tear it up
I could catch a groove like a flash in the dark
Grab a hold of your attention like a thief in the park
'cause I can flip a rhyme off the tip of my tongue
Switching up the rhythm like the rhyme's a piece of chewing gum
Now I might chew but i don't bite
My ideas are mine when I begin to write
In my sleep I'll be thinking 'bout beats
And getting on the mic and busting some treats
And sporting the crazy funky threads that you've never even seen before
What I'm lacking from the macking i can find at the thrift store
I won't scuff nor scuffle just grin as they walk by
Take time to rhyme for a girl I hear talk fly
Down some papaya down with the revolution
Always wear my goggles 'cause there's so much pollution
I can do the freak, the patty duke and the spank
Gotta free the funky fish from the funky fish tanks
I'll sell my house, sell my car and I'll sell all my stuff
I'm going back to new york city I do believe i've had enough</song>
      <song title="So What'cha Want" track="7">Just plug me in just like I was eddie harris
You're eating crazy cheese like you'd think I'm from paris
You know I get fly you think i get high
You know that I'm gone and i'm a tell you all why
So tell me who are you dissing maybe I'm missing
The reason that you're smiling or wilding
So listen in my head I just want to take 'em down
Imagination set loose and I'm gonna shake 'em down
Let it flow like a mud slide
When I get on i like to ride and glide
I've got depth of perception in my text y'all
I get props at my mention 'cause I vex y'all
So what'cha want
I get so funny with the money that you flaunt
I said where'd you get your information from huh?
You think that you can front when revelation comes

Yeh, you can't front on that

Well they call me mike d the ever loving man
I'm like spoonie gee well I'm the metropolitician
You scream and you holler about my chevy impala
But the sweat is getting wet around the ring around your collar
But like a dream I'm flowing without no stopping 
Sweeter than a cherry pie with ready whip topping
Goin' from mic to mic kickin' it wall to wall
Well I'll be calling out you people like a casting call
Well it's wack when you're jacked in the back of a ride
With your know with your flow when you're out getting by
Believe me what you see is what you get
And you see me I'm coming off as you can bet
Well I think i'm losing my mind this time
This time I'm losing my mind
That's right, said I think i'm losing my mind this time
This time I'm losing my mind

Yeh, you can't front on that

But little do you know about something that I talk about
I'm tired of driving it's due time that I walk about
But in the meantime, I'm wise to the demise
I've got eyes in the back of my head so I realize
Well I'm dr. spock i'm here to rock y'all
I want you off the wall if you're playing the wall
I said what'cha want
Y'all suckers write me checks and then they bounce
So I reach into my pocket for the fresh amount
See I'm the long leaner vincent the cleaner
I'm the illest motherfucker from here to gardena
I'm as cool as a cucumber in a bowl of hot sauce
You've got the rhyme and reason but no cause
Well if you're hot to trot you think you're slicker than grease
I've got news for you crews you'll be sucking like a leach

You can't front on that
So what'cha want</song>
      <song title="The Biz V. The Nuge" track="8">The beatsie boys they are they're comin' home
They're comin' home they're comin' home
Oh they're comin' home</song>
      <song title="Time For Livin'" track="9">Yeah, that's right
It's time to set the record straight

Ain't nobody got to spell it for me
Ain't nobody got to yell I can see
Ain't nobody got the pain I can hear
But if I have to i'll yell in your ear

Time for living
Time for giving &lt;i&gt;[x4]&lt;/i&gt;

Ain't nobody to to spell it for me
I said ain't nobody got to yell I can see
I said ain't nobody got the pain I can hear
But if I have to i will yell in your ear

Soul fire
Soul fire
And we ain't got no water
We don't got no water

Time for living time for giving
No time for making up a monster to sell
Time for living time for giving
No time for breakin' out a lie to sell</song>
      <song title="Something's Got To Give" track="10">I wish for peace between the races
Someday we shall all be one
Why fight yourself
This one's called rectify
There's something coming to the surface
There's fire all around
But this is an illusion

I've seen better days than this one
I've seen better nights than this one
Tension is rebuilding
Something's got to give
Something's got to give

Someday we shall all be one

Jesus christ we're nice</song>
      <song title="Stand Together" track="11">I don't see things quite the same as I used to
As I live my life I've got just me to be true to
And when I find that i don't know about just what to do
I turn and look within to see what I should do
Now I'm not sure what it takes to be hip
A lot of people making music that to be ain't shit
So I ask creation For rhymes for this jam
Gimme lickle solo and I'll take the mic stand

Love vibe 

As the earth spins into brand new day
I see the light on the horizons's not fading away
Gonna shine from within like a bright white sun
No need to hide and no place to run
Got the vibrations of the music
Bringing light to your mind
So you can move and groove
And feel the beat of the time
Sense the power in the air as it starts to move
You get a real good feeling that you just can't lose

Contemplation time, intuition time
Evolution time, resolution time

Free your mind it's time for good times
And let yourself move it's a time to shine
Spread your wings in the sky, feelin' good inside
Breaking fool with no need to hide
I got the music cuttin' throught me
Takin' control of my soul
I can't hold back I've got to let go

Stand together people come together now
It's about time we've got to get together y'all</song>
      <song title="Pow" track="12">Pow!</song>
      <song title="The Maestro" track="13">Who is the man coming down your block
It's me you see with the funk in my walk
'Cause I'm doin' just what I like to
Today is my day and I'm a get nice too
You gotta keep movin' and you can't say nothing
I'm a keep bouncin' and bumpin' and stuffin'
One thing you ought to know---I am the maestro

&lt;i&gt;[Speech]&lt;/i&gt;

I feel like Rufus Thomas The crown prince of dance
I'm mike d and I'm known for romance
I'm the crazy baldhead with the part on the side
And I'm riding down the block Like I'm on a water slide
'Cause it's the type of day I feel like pressing my luck
'Cause I got nothing to lose 'Cause I don't give a fuck
See I'm a player I play Don't play to win I play to show
I am the maestro!

&lt;i&gt;[Routine, then speech]&lt;/i&gt;
Who is the man.</song>
      <song title="Live At P.J.'s" track="14">Well,
Back to the beat y'all,
Down with the sound so sweet y'all
Just how fresh can you get y'all
Those that are blessed say yes y'all
'Cause I'm a come inside and do my thing
I'm gonna take off my drawers and let myself swing
Tantalize my tummy with a boo boo snack
But now I got to get back

Gonna break it down to the nitty grit
Gonna tell you motherfuckers Why you ain't shit
'Cause suckers like you Just make me strong
When you're popping that bullshit all day long

I'm gonna bust my shoes I'm gonna bust my socks
I'm gonna spread my word From standing on this box
This drive through world it just ain't right
Gonna run to Joe and Tony's And get my hair cut nice

Well come on y'all and let's work it out
I'm trying to get up So don't you get me down
Life I love you now give me a pound
Up from the frying pan into the fire
Look within and try to admire, yeh
What's going on Y'all</song>
      <song title="Mark On The Bus" track="15">Good morning, time to get up and go to work
I ride on the bus into the city everyday
I sit on my seat and I dream myself away
I dream I'm on an island with that foxy lady too
But when I awaken i must be mistaken i'm on third avenue
Won't you take me away and take away me
Won't you take me away and take away me</song>
      <song title="Professor Booty" track="16">Yes, I got more bounce to the fuckin' bump
And then you want to know
Why it's cause I'm motherfuckin' truckin'
I'm in the pocket just like Grady Tate
I got supplies of beats so you don't have to wait
'Cause I'm the master blaster
Drinking up the shasta
My voice sounds sweet 'cause it has to
So light a match to my ass 'cause I'm blown up
I'd like to thank the people for just showin' up
But now I want y'all to move it
Put your point on the floor and just prove it
And I'm smurfin not rehearsin' gettin' live y'all
A little puffy so you know what I'm doin' right
'Cause that's the kind of frame of mind I'm in
I got this feelin' and it's back again
So don't touch me 'cause I'm electric
And if you touch me you'll get shocked!

You've got the boomin' system But it's blasting out doo-doo
You think it's chocolate milk But it's watered down yoo-hoo
I've been through many times In which I thought I might lose it
The only thing that saved me Has always been music
We've got our own studio the son of the G
It's no question life's been good to me
'Cause life ain't nothing but a good groove
A good mix tape to put you in the right mood
This one goes out to my man the Groove Merchant
Coming through with beats For which I've been searching
Like two sealed copies of expansions
I'm like tom vu with yachts and mansions
The logo I sport is the face of the monkey
Union made ben davis quality it's no junk see
My chrome is shining just like an icicle
I ride around town on my low-rider bicycle

So many wack M.C.'s You get the T.V. bozack
Ain't even gonna call out your names 'Cause you're so wack
But one big oaf whose faker than plastic
A dictionary definition of the word spastic
You should have never started something That you couldn't finish
'Cause writin' rhymes to me Is like Popeye to spinach
I'm bad ass move your fat ass 'Cause you're wack son
Dancin' around like you think you're Janet Jackson
Thought you could walk on me To get some ground to walk on
I'll put the rug out under your ass As I talk on
I'll take you out like a sniper on a roof
Like an M.C. at the fever in the D.J. booth
With your headphones strapped You're rockin' rewind pause
Tryin' to figure out what you can do to go for yours
But like the pencil to the paper I got more to come
One after another you can all get some
So you getter take your time And meditate on your rhyme
'Cause your shit'll be stinking When I go for mine
And that's right y'all don't get uptight y'all
You can't say shit Because you're biting what I write y'all
And that's wrong y'all over the long haul
You can't cut the mustard When you're fronting it all</song>
      <song title="Namaste" track="17">A butterfly floats on the breeze of a sun lit day
As I feel this reality gently fade away
Riding on a thought to see where it's from
Gliding through a memory of a time yet to come
Smoke paints the air Swirling images through my mind
Like a whirlpool spin beginning to unwind
And I stand at the edge cautiously awaiting
As time slips by
Carefully navigating by the stars in the sky
And I sit And I think to myself
And on the horizon the sun light begins to climb
And it seems like it's been so long since he shined
But I'm sure it was only yesterday

Namaste 

A cold chill of fear cut through me
I felt my heart contract
To my mind I brought the image of light
And I expanded out of it
My fear was just a shadow
And then a voice spoke in my head
And she said dark is not the opposite of light
It's the absence of light
And I thought to myself
She knows what she's talking about
And for a moment I know
What it was all about.</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Hello Nasty" year="1998">
      <song title="Super Disco Breakin'" track="1">Well it's 50 cups of coffee and you know it's on
I move the crowd to the break of break of dawn
Can't rock the house without the party people
Cause when we're gettin down we are all equal
There's no better or worse between you and me
But I rock the mic so viciously
Like pins and needles and words that sting
At the blink of an eye I will do my thing
It's Like a needle in the cartridge when the record spins
Like diggin down deep in the record bins
Everybody gettin down make no mistake
Nothing sounds quite like an 8 0 8

Money makin money money makin manhattan
Super disco disco breakin'
Money makin money money makin manhattan
Super disco disco breakin'

Sometimes I like to brag sometimes I'm soft spoken
When I'm in Holland I eat the pannenkoeken
World is the the spice you bring the sauce
You can kiss my ass you funky boss
Now that you got what you want, you want more
I'll be with the hammer and the nail at your door
With these funky beats I be goin' head huntin'
Shouts to my peeps let me know if you feel something
Cause I can give you all you need
A little beat for the rhythm and some words to read
Let me tell you now that's my favorite shit
And when I got a new rhyme i just say it
So money makin money money makin manhattan
Super disco disco breakin'
Money makin money money makin manhattan
Super disco disco breakin'</song>
      <song title="The Move" track="2">Yo..Hello.. 
It's times like this when I just can't stop
Can't wind your body without the body rock
Got schemes schematics blue prints on file
You gotta have dreams to make it all worthwhile
So as I take my time and realign
I wonder what it is I hope to find
I don't mean to brag I don't mean to boast
But I'm intercontinental when I eat french toast
Adrock with the New Edition
Gettin on down for the year 2000
A slight distraction can get you paid
And when it comes to that type shit I paved the way

BBoys to the early morn
BGirls be rockin on and on
BGirls to the break of dawn
BBoys be rockin on and on

Dogs love me cause I'm crazy sniffable
I bet you never knew I got the ill peripheral
In your home I'm cloned I'm on your headphones
I love it when you spazz out all alone
Cause I'm that fool that broke the key
I'm unlockable so don't check me
Got weight on my shoulders and things on my mind
The sky is falling and I'm falling behind
So I synthesize sounds as I patch my brain
Insane mind games move quick like flames
So now I wonder how sometimes you never know
Who be rockin y'all in stereo in stereo in stereo in stereo

No time like the present to work shit out
That's what I'm going on and on and on about
Not fakin just makin beats in the dungeon
Keep that shit funky cause the odor is pungent
No shame in my game just par for the path
I try to hone my craft because at hands the task
But I find I'm not playing with a full deck
I'm up to my neck like Toulouse Lautrec
All I wanna know is when is checkout time
So I could be in heaven with the rhythm rock rhyme
And when I'm with my man shadi rock at the gates
We'll be rockin rhythms over disco breaks

BBoys to the early morn
BGirls be rockin on and on
BGirls to the break of dawn
BBoys be rockin on and on

&lt;i&gt;[Spanish Crap]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Remote Control" track="3">Things get hectic quick
From the satellite dish to your joy stick
It's the night of the living cable box
Wires coming up from around the block
Remote control to change the station
But that won't change your situation
Have you seen what I mean
I'm the little gnome that's in your dreams
So I say this rhyme built by design
To take you beyond space and time
Said who is the man making diamonds out of coal
The man pushing buttons on remote control

Remote I want Control
Remote I want Control

Until your back's up against the wall
You never know yourself that much at all
So you've got to share your love with a friend
That's all that you've got left in the end
Living in this city of pure confusion
People misled by their own illusion
All this action, no satisfaction
We're all linked together like a chain reaction
Play or fold, love is bold
What is the future that will unfold? 
Some like it hot, others like it cold
But we all want to hold the remote control

Remote I want Control
Remote I want Control
Remote I want Control
Remote I want Control

Things get hectic quick
All of the sudden I'm in the thick
Too much drama all around
Distractions booming in sensuround
Like a rainy day's Earth won't sit still
Sliding on down a hill
Sometimes life it seems to stall
So never be ungrateful y'all
So I got a little something for your pay per view
Like don king I've got the crazy hair do
We've got cameras on Mars on space patrol
Controlled on earth by remote control</song>
      <song title="Song For The Man" track="4">What makes you feel
And why you gotta be
Like you got the right
To look her up and down
What makes this world
So sick and evil

I know you don't know

What makes you feel
Like you got (Miracle) Whip appeal
Who made you the judge an jury
Ain't you never heard of privacy
What makes this world
So sick and evil

You figure it out</song>
      <song title="Just A Test" track="5">Like a flag at half mast as frames click fast
Not a thing will last as past is past
Like stacks of thoughts that got played and worn
Used over and over till they were tired and torn
Like a broken clock that can't tell time
Like a thick ass book that's filled with wack rhymes
Like a scorching blaze that burned the sand
Like a band that planned and planned and planned
And flew down like a raven in the dark of night
And snatched up the worm helpless to fight
And brought it back to the nest singing microphone check
One two one two this is just a test

Like sand in one hand You can't hold for long
Like scheming on a plan that goes all wrong
Like fudge and caramel they're not the same
And it's a shame all you talk is game
You act like a diamond waiting to be set
In a gold ring, as if, I bet
As time goes by in this give and take
As long as I learn I will make mistakes
What do I want? what do i need? 
Why do I want it? what's in it for me? 
It's the imagery of technology
Is what you get is what you see
Don't worry your mind 
When you give it your best
One two one two this is just a test</song>
      <song title="Body Movin'" track="6">Ready, one.
You will do this four times with the left
Four with the right
Then eight times with both
Then repeat.

Body movin, body movin
A-1 sound, sound so soothing
Body movin, body movin
We be getting down and you know we're crush groovin.

Now Let me get some action from the back section
We need body rocking not perfection
Let your back bone flip but dont slip a disc
Let your spine unwind just take a risk
I wanna do the freak until the break of dawn
Now, tell me party people is that so wrong
The ship is docking, inter-lockin
And up-rockin electro-shocking
We're getting down computer action
Do the robotic satisfaction
All of y'all get off the wall
Have a ball and get involved with

Body movin, body movin
with the a-1 sound sound so soothing
Body movin, body movin
We be getting down and you know we're crush groovin.

Stand erect, arms down, 
Swing left arm big same with the right

Flame on, I'm gone
I'm so sweet like a nice bon bon
Came out rapping when I was born
Mom said rock it 'til the break of dawn
Puttin bodies in motion cause I got the notion
Like roy cormier with the coconut lotion
The sound of music makin you insane 
You can't explain to people this type of mind frame 
Like a bottle of Chateau Neuf Du Pap
I'm fine like wine when I start to rap
We need body rockin not perfection
Let me get some action from the back section

Body movin, body movin 
A-1 sound, sound so soothing
Body movin, body movin 
We be getting down and you know we're crush groovin

Left arm ready and one,
and again, stand erect

Mike D with the master plan
I said ooh my my and thank you ma'am 
And when I grab the mic you scream ooh god damn
The creme de la creme is who I am
MCA where have you been
Packed like sardines in the tin
So kick off your shoes and put on your swim fins
Cause when it comes to quarries I'm known to swim
And Adrock light up the place
And if you pull my card you pull the ace
And if you ask me to turn up the bass
And if you play defender I could be your hyper space

Body movin, body movin
with the a-1 sound sound so soothing
Body movin, body movin 
We be getting down and you know we're crush groovin.

You will do eight hops on the left, eight on the right
Four left four right, two left, two right
then one each: left, right, left, right 
start and land on the balls of the feet 
left foot, ready, it's one, two, three, four, five.</song>
      <song title="Intergalactic" track="7">Intergalactic planetary planetary intergalactic
Another dimension, another dimension

Well Now don't you tell me to smile
You stick around I'll make it worth your while
Got numbers beyond what you can dial
Maybe it's because I'm so versatile
Style profile I said
It always brings me back when I hear Ooh Child
From the hudson river out to the nile 
I run the marathon til the very last mile
If you battle me I will revile
People always say my style is wild
You've got gall you've got guile 
To step to me I'm a rapophile
If you want to battle your in denial
Coming from uranus to check my style
Go ahead put my rhymes on trial
Cast you off into exile

Intergalactic planetary
Planetary intergalactic

Jazz and awol that's our team
Step inside the party disrupt the whole scene
When it comes to beats well I'm a fiend
I like my sugar with coffee and cream
Well I got to keep it going keep it going full steam
Too sweet to be sour too nice to be mean
On the tough guy style I'm not too keen
To try to change the world I will plot and scheme
Mario C likes to keep it clean
Gonna shine like a sun beam
Keep on rapping cause that's my dream
Got an a from moe dee for sticking to themes
When it comes to envy y'all is green
Jealous of the rhyme and the rhyme routine
Another dimension new galaxy
Intergalactic planetary

Intergalactic planetary
Planetary intergalactic

From the family tree of old school hip hop
Kick off your shoes and relax your socks
The rhymes will spread just like a pox
Cause the music is live like an electric shock
I am known to do the Wop
Also known for the Flintstone Flop 
Tammy D getting biz on the crop
Beastie Boys known to let the beat... drop
When I wrote graffiti my name was Slop
If my rap's soup my beats is stock
Step from the tables as I start to chop
I'm a lumber jack DJ Adrock
If you try to knock me you'll get mocked
I'll stir fry you in my wok
Your knees'll start shaking and your fingers pop
Like a pinch on the neck of Mr. Spock 

Intergalactic planetary
Planetary intergalactic
Another dimension do it</song>
      <song title="Putting Shame In Your Game" track="8">Beatsie beatsie boys gettin live on the spot
Puttin all kinds of shame in the game you've got
We keep the party movin to the broad day light
g.e.t.l.i.v.e. alright

Transhypnotic robotic can't stop it
No limits to this style and you know you can't lock it
First you mock it, rock it and then you stock it
But I've got the styles that are always in the pocket
Like a bird floating down on a New York breeze 
Every thought in the mind is a planted seed
So watch the mind or the thoughts will stack
Before you know it they're boomeranging on back
I'm the king of Boggle there is none higher
I get 11 points off the word quagmire
Fools can't see me and that's how it is
And that's how I like it cause that's my biz

Beatsie beatsie boys gettin live on the spot
Puttin all kinds of shame in the game you've got
We keep the party movin to the broad day light
g.e.t.l.i.v.e. alright

Time's an illusion as the moments race by
Too fast to really grasp though we may try
Deny, till we die, ooh my my
These thoughts that mislead and then multiply
Well second by second and minute by minute
It's like lotto you gotta be in it to win it
Shakin mind breakin on their own demise
Lies tax to the max and they'll be feelin those vibes
So tell me what you need that you have got
Fiending on power will make your blood clot
It starts with the greed and then goes all wrong
That's why we can't all just get along
We're all connected like a Lego set
One equaling one together like a croquette
Whether we have or have not yet met
It ain't no thing and it ain't no sweat

Beatsie beatsie boys gettin live on the spot
Puttin all kinds of shame in the game you've got
We keep the party movin to the broad day light
g.e.t.l.i.v.e. alright
Nonstop Hip-Hop

You're caught in a panic and it's rattled your brain
The selfish ways just can't maintain
But these are the breaks when you try and come fake
Don't come with the rhymes that you just half baked
I'm the benihana chef on the sp12
I chop the fuck out the beats left on the shelf
You be like hello nasty where you been
It's time you brought the grimy beats out the dungeon
I jumped outside the house with my Walkman on
I get so hyped when I hear this song
It's gonna keep me happy like all day long
So go and talk shit cause it just makes me strong
Don't grease my palm with your filthy cash
Multinationals spreading like a rash
I might stick around or I might be a fad
But I won't sell my songs for no TV ad 

Beatsie beatsie boys gettin live on the spot
Puttin all kinds of shame in the game you got
We keep the party movin to the broad day light
g.e.t.l.i.v.e. alright
Junior</song>
      <song title="Flowin' Prose" track="9">I'm flowing prose to cons and cons to pros
I'm scheming rhyme against reason like it was flow against know
But beyond the concepts and emotions that rise
To the interconnectedness that underlies
The lies upon lies have lost their meaning
The plies upon plies of consciousness that is being
Over and over I fall I learned to walk from a crawl
It's not sad it's just the way and the purpose of it all

Now every word that you heard that I said that you felt
Was put in place in the space as they were shuffled and dealt
I steal feels from reels but I pay my respects
Paying compliments and disses and deciphering affects
Words are water as I court her, as she is pristine
Words and mics fall to dust and all that's left is the feelings
I give in and I win I try to never complain
Intentions venture to center and then they set the stage
But I'll remain sane making gain without pain
Staining trains with names and driving lanes to the refrain
And keep it positive as painstaking as it is
I'll never turn back cause that's the way I've got to live 

So like a cloud carries rain I'm gonna carry my rhyme
Coming like thunder with lightening timing
No hesitation in gestation of thoughts and plans
Ferment time like wine no ploys or scams
Like the islands dot the oceans in the endless seas
Ideas coming to me in answer to my pleas
Woke up this morning right out of a dream
Reached for my pen and pad because my mind was on a rhyme scheme
What can I do with these bones and flesh? 
With these animated thoughts in a world repressed?
I'm going down like the rhythms on the winds of change
I'm keeping calm under pressure like a deep-sea range
I'm flowing prose to cons and cons to pros
I'm like toucan sam when I follow my nose
I'm giving shouts to Gandhi, Gravy and King 
His Holiness and all enlightened beings
I'll be the one who screams it on the microphone
I'll be the one who brings it inside your home 
But the words ain't mine I just pass em along
For betty williams and her friends I sing this song
And more ink from my pen and more tears from my eyes
And more crimes are committed as I say these lines </song>
      <song title="And Me" track="10">Once again I'm all wrapped up in me
My best friend's my own worst enemy
Electricity and gravity

Oh my god now take a look at me
My life line's run by AT&amp;T
They got their wires all up in me
Is push and pull the way it's got to be

Once again I'm all wrapped up in me and me</song>
      <song title="Three MC's And One DJ" track="11">Cause nobody can do it like Mix Master can, 
Come on now
I've got the D double O, D double O style
Here we go again because it's been awhile
Do me a favor don't touch that dial
I rock from Manhattan to the miracle mile
My name's mike d and I'm the ladies choice
I want to get next to you like Rose Royce
Y'all gather round to hear my golden voice
Cause when its time to rhyme you know I get noice
Cruising like a fan boat on the glade 
He'll tweak your ass across the cross fade
So watch your back when he takes the stage
Or he'll send you off on a naked rampage

3 MC's and one DJ
We be getting down with no delay
Mix master mike what cha got to say
Bug out/to the mic/all the time

Sweet and sour like a tangerine
Fresh like a box of Krispy Kremes
Kenny rogers' gambler is my gambling theme
Mix master mike with the scratch routine
Always updated and in the know 
You know we break it down going toe to toe
The bass is booming from down below 
And Norton is chillin with Mario
Well my name is Adrock I'm a Scorpio
Don't ask me cause I just don't know
I'm known to mop I'm known to glow 
But don't get mad cause I got to go

Three MC's and one DJ
We be getting down with no delay
Mix master mike what cha got to say 
Gotta get down

Mix Master cut faster

All top secret and classified
I grab a hold of a mic and let the words glide
It's all hypnotic and sanctified
I never wanna let a bad day slip by
Now We be getting stupid in your area 
Causing all kinds of hysteria
My beats is sick like malaria
But don't worry I'll take care of ya
Me and adam adam and mario c
In the studio it's the place to be
To all party people who are happy and free
With mix master mike we're making history

Three MC's and one DJ
We be getting down with no delay
Mix master mike what you got to say
Goddamn that dj made my day</song>
      <song title="The Grasshopper Unit (Keep Movin')" track="12">Dear Alex and Marilyn
They're Lovey and Thurston howellin
The grasshopper unit is prowellin
And Rufus is back home growellin
For all of y'all that are dozin
On Hornblower's lederhosen
Like walt disney he is frozen
And then the Swiss Hall of Fame he goes in
Cause when he's out in space carousin
Pick up my mic and start joustin
My name plate medallion
Says never trust a hal 9000

Can't, won't, don't stop rockin to the rhythm 'cause I get down cause i

Check the horizontal hold and check the tint
Are these three fools back at it again
Inspector Clouseau and Derek Flint
Nothin but sparks ignitin'
Check two one two mic testin
This one goes out to Dechen
Rise fallen fighters take your stance again
Don't think too much about the color of skin
Order in vegetarian sharks fin
Try to keep my life non violent
Mario Rewind the tape and punch him in
Like chuck d with the where you never been I'm in

Can't, won't, don't stop rockin to the rhythm 'cause I get down cause i get
I'm a long way from where I've been but I gotta keep movin', movin on

Ooh my my I'm really not feeling it
Ooh my my something's really wrong
The p.a. sound is deafenin
Bitin mcs I'm oustinin
With spinach in your teeth you're grinnin
So on your way out please take a mint
Got the studio to throw a craze in
The basslines yauch just lays in
This song is the grass you're grazin
Add a little flange and phase in
Don't get mad 'cause I'm beguilin
I'm off the hook so don't bother dialin
They're gonna put me in the b.i.n. 
And if I die notify the next of kin

It's like that y'all
Can't, won't, don't stop</song>
      <song title="Song For Junior" track="13">I'm hypnotized by you</song>
      <song title="I Don't Know" track="14">What's pleasing to the eye
In the delusion of my sight
Is not what I find when I reach into the light
I have lost my mind
I'm walking through time
Deluded as the next guy
Pretending and hoping to find
That distant peace of mind

I don't know
Who does know
There is no 
Where to go

It's not so simple as I try to wish
But then again what is?
There is no other worthy quest
So on I go

I don't know
Who does know
There is no 
Where to go</song>
      <song title="The Negotiation Limerick File" track="15">My DJ's got the cuts and the beats are on
We're comin with the limericks and we're comin' strong
And the rhythm's on time to every word and rhyme
When it comes to keep it real I keep it really wrong
At the risk of sounding crass I would like to mention
That I am well aware of your wack intentions
To usurp my prose you so and so
It's my primary bone of contention
I tell you everybody I've had it
With all these people with static
I'll go insane if it don't rain
Sucker MC's are problematic
I love it when you hit those switches
A curve ball's what my pitch is
So here we here we come
Like dum ditty dum
I keep all five boroughs in stitches

The sound sounds sweeter through the echolex
It'll spin you around and throw you in a hex
Until you feel no pain inside your brain
All your worries are soothed by the sound effects
You ead it in the Post and the Daily News
Listen everybody lets show improve
Don't let me begin about heroin
Living six feet deep just ain't the move
We're giving you soul power
I like it sweet and sour
When it comes to rhymes and beat designs
I'm at the control tower
Tell me what makes you so afraid
Of all those people you say you hate
Just give it one time for your mind
And let's try to negotiate &lt;i&gt;[3x]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Electrify" track="16">Words comin forth like water from the tap
Clap tracks line the spaces places papers people stack
Back track through the minutes when the thoughts went insane
I pulled the picture off the cover and blew out the mind games
People say this is the playlist of the void non-bound
But I can say this is the plainness of the peace I've found
It's not the sorrow or the pity that we hope to dismantle
It's the cast of past dice lighting both ends of the candles
Scandelescent in the means I have dreamed on the schemes
Reunited in the times of such picturesque scenes
Can I get a witness to testify
Open your eyes realize electrify

Electrify

So I plan and I scam and write it off on my taxes
It's times like these I'll just go with the decisions of the masses
And to the crowds who've come before with their profit massing ways
To the greed that fucked it up and brought it down to today
With pain I stand sane and remain holding strong
Whilst all around me those who clowned me are now drowning by the throngs
It's illogical the actions that are typically displayed
A set back ain't all that much problem to invade
So I will glow like a lantern on a new moon night
I'll fight violence with these hands that weren't built to fight
But like a furnace burning coal my goals are bound to burn in flames
Whether achieved or dismantled by the agendas displayed
Can I get a witness to testify?
Open your eyes realize electrify

Electrify</song>
      <song title="Picture This" track="17">Something on the windowsill
Caught her eye and held her still
The cars pass by outside
Nowhere left to hide

Picture this now crystal clear
Nothing left to hold her here
And creeping up meanwhile
Traces of a smile
Something on the windowsill
Caught her eye and held her still
The cars pass by outside
Eyes open wide to see if I could fly

Something on the windowsill
Something on the windowsill</song>
      <song title="Unite" track="18">Goin off the hook like Latrell Spreewell
I've got the ill technique so you know me be well
We be kickin bass all up in your face
And when it comes to beats well I'm the rhythm ace
Now if you check my pulse it beats skull snaps
I keep all my rhymes in my Le Sportsac
So what if I'm a ham and cheese on rye
I got to do my thing and that's no lie
Well ice is cold and fire is hot
When it comes to competition we've got them locked
U.N.I.T.E. 
A little shout to Ian and little Zoe
One can wonder why but can't deny
If we could work it out it would be so fly
We'll never know unless we try
So tell me party people what's your zodiac sign

Breakdancers of the world unite
BBoys of the world unite

I went inside the deli and my man's like what
I write the songs that make the whole world suck
I need to break it down every chance I get
So &quot;Ssshhh we keep it raw on the set&quot;
Automation circulation
This is for the people all around the nations
I got books with hooks and it looks like rain
Would someone on the Knicks please drive the lane
Now rhymes are montaquilla on a track by us
I've got to keep my mind clear so I don't bust
If you got bad breath then maybe try Scope
And if you wash your ass you best use soap
People of the world you realize
We got to get together and harmonize
I feel I'm comin down with the bugallo flu
Explain to me really what doctors must do, I said

Ravers of the world unite

We're the scientists of sound
We're mathematically puttin' it down
When lightning strikes best grab a ground
Got to get up to get down
I've got the Terminator style with a touch of the tweak
Technique 1200's I'm known to freak
I don't like to fight, I don't carry a piece
I wear permanent press so I'm always creased
Mike D, with the rump shakin action
Do it like this for the intergalaction
I smoke daily so I'm very flexible
I'm a scorpio so you know I'm very sexual
Shouts to rach and my brother matthew
In money makin it's how we do
I be smokin roaches in the vestibule
In the next millennium I'll still be old school (Ron) 
High roller big baller
I call em crullers but you know they're called CRAWLERS
We keep it movin to the broad day light
BGirls of the world unite alright

Keep it on and on</song>
      <song title="Instant Death" track="19">And what do you do when 
Your own man kills himself and
How do I make friends now

And where is my Mom
I need to show her that
She taught me

And please let me
Die an instant death</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Ill Communication" year="1994">
      <song title="Sure Shot" track="1">You can't, you won't and you don't stop
Mike d come on and rock the sure shot

I've got the brand new doo-doo guaranteed like yoo hoo
I'm on like dr john, yea mr zu zu
I'm a newlywed, not a divorcee
And everything I do is funky like lee dorsey
Well, it's the taking fo pelham, one, two, three
If you want a doodoo rhyme then come see me
I've got the savior faire with the unique rhyme and
I keep it on and on, it's never quitting time and
Strictly hand held is the style I go
Never rock the mic with the panty hose
I strap on my ear goggles and I'm ready to go
'couse at the boards is the man they call the mario
Pull up at the function and you know I kojak
To all the party people that are on my bozak
I've got more action than my man john woo
And I've got mad hits like i was rod carew

You can't, you won't and you don't stop
Ad rock come and rock the sure shot

Hurricane will cross fade on your ass and bust your ear drums
Listen everybody 'couse I'm shifting gears i'm 
Fresh like dougie when I set my specs and
On the microphone I come correct
Timing like a clock when I'rock the hip hop
Top notch is my stock on the soap box
I've got more rhymes than I'v got grey hairs
And that's alot because I've got my share
I've got a hole in my head and there's no one to fix it
Got to straighten my thoughts, I'm thinking too much sick shit
Everyone just takes and takes, takes, takes, takes
I've got to step back, I've got to contemplate
I'm like lee perry, I'm very
On rock the microphone and then I'm gone
I'm like vaughn bode, I'm a cheech wizard
Never quitting, so won't you listen

Oh yes indeed, it's fun time
'cause you can't, you won't and you don't stop
Mca come and rock the sure shot

I want to say a little something that's long overdue
The disrespect to women has got to be through
To all the mothers and sisters and the wives and friends
I want to offer my love and respect to the end
Well you say I'm twenty something and should be slacking
But I'm working harder than ever and you could call it macking
So I'm supposed to sit upon my couch watching my T.V.
I'm still iistening to wax, I'm not using the cd
I'm that kid in the corner
All fucked up and I wanna so i'm gonna
Take a piece of the pie, why not, I'm not quitting
Think I'm gonna change up my style just to fit in
I keep my underwear up with a piece of elastic
I use a bullshit mic that's made out of plastic
To send my rhymes out to all nations
Like ma bell, I've got the ill communications

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Tough Guy" track="2">Butcher me on the court
Too many elbows to report
Now you're poking me in the eye
Bill laimbeer motherfucker, it's time for you to die

Tough guy, it's time to check yourself
Dribbling the ball like the biz can be bad for your health
Tough guy, what you got to prove
Moving like an elephant, that's your favorite move
Tough guy, your shit is going out

Tough Guy 

Box me out with your fat ass
Throw me around like a bounce pass
You've got a tombstone hanging over your dick
Cause a minor earthquake when you throw a moving pick

Touch guy, you think you're like the shaq
Keep running around, you'll catch a heart attack
Tough guy, what are you giving me
The way you're playing ball, you'll stop me from living b

Tough guy, tough guy

Tough guy, you're shit is weak
Tough guy, you fucking freak
Tough guy, I'll stick your shit
Tough Guy</song>
      <song title="B-Boys Makin' With the Freak Freak" track="3">Putting songs together ain't no puzzle like yahtzee
Sending this out to k-rob and rahmalzee
Let me introduce myself on this cut
I'm ad rock, I'm lit like a motherfuck
Well, I'm brewing up rhymes like i was using a still
Kickin' an old school flow like mike mcgill
'cause yauch's on the upright, the shit just ain't funny
Got fat bass lines like russel simmons steals money
Got clientele, you know I rock well
And then you're on my dick because I'm D.F.L.
Yeah, mike 'cause playing the bass is my favorite shit
I might be a hack on the stand up but I'm working at it
I get my hair cut correct like anthony mason
Then I ride the I.R.T. right up to penn station
Penn station up on 8th ave.
Listen all y'all you get the ball bath
He's got the savior faire because he's debonair
Mike d with the vinyl with the grooves so rare
And the rhymes that we're are doo doo

Shit, if it's going to be that kind of a party
I'm gonna stick my dick in the mashed potatoes

Been makin' with the freak freak, so unique
I been learning from the elders now it's time to speak
Oh that shit sounds nice
Mike d come on and get it on y'all
Talking shit about a mile a minute
Put the wax on the table and let the D.J. spin it
Excuse me motherfuckers, can I beg your pardon
I'm gonna see the knicks at madison square garden
And like the knicks I got game like i worked at hasbro
On the mic I bug, like i was prince jazzbo
The rhymes are stupid to make you go coo-coo
You can't sleep 'cause you're little cindy loo hoo
Down with the hurra since the raising hell tour
Just listen to his cuts there's no reason to tell more
Cindy what I didn't catch the last one
That shit sounded kinda nice, but bust a fast one
Well I'm not known for my speed raps
So grab the microphone and cut out the claps
Ah yea, I like that shit is kind of rough
I'll grab the microphone and fuck it up

I might seem out there, a little deranged
I've got to cool off, catch me on the driving range
Well I'm the ladies' choise like i was J.J. evans
Legalize the weed and I'll say thank heavens
I'm talking P.G.A. pro tour 2
I'm doctor beppers in my T.V., in my golfing shoes
Pass me an iron and I'll bust a chip shot
Then you throw me off the green because I'm strictly hip-hop
I'll grab the tee, I'll tee off
I'll grab the golf clubs and I'm off, i'm audi- so check me
I've got the timbos on my toes when I'm not on the green
I've got the costom made boots with the spikey things
I'm working on my driving 'cause I'm going pro
I've got the funky fly golf gear from head to toe
Yea, the b-boys makin' with the freak freak
Mario's nagging nonni's about the pesto pizza
And then he's on a mission and he's checking for peacha</song>
      <song title="Root Down" track="4">I kick it root down
I put my root down

It's not a put down
I put my foot down
And then I make some love, i put my root down
Like sweetie pie by the stone alliance
Everbody knows I'm known for dropping science
I'm electric like dick hyman
I guess you'd expect to catch the crew rhymin'
Never let you down with the stereo sound
So mike, get on the mic and turn it out
We're talking root down, I put my boot down
And if you want to battle me, you're putting loot down
I said root down, it's time to scoot down
I'm a step up to the mic in my goose down
Come up representing from the upper west
Money makin' putting me to the test
Sometimes I feel as though i've been blessed
Because I'm doing what i want so i never rest
Well, I'm not coming out goofy like the fruit of the loom guys
Just strutting like the meters with the look-ka py py
'cause downtown brooklyn is where I was born 
But when the snow is falling, then I'm gone
You might think that I'm a fanatic
A phone call from utah and I'm throwing a panic
But we break it from the root when we kick it on down
Jimmy smith is my man, I want to give him a pound

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Ad rock don't stop, just get on the mic with the tic and the toc
I'll fill you with the fuckin' rim like brim
I'm walking down your block and you say that's him
There goes the guy with the funky sound
The beastie boys you know we come to get down
Because I've got the flow where i grab my dick
And say oh my god, that's the funky shit
So I'm going to pass the mic and cause a panic
The original nasal kid is doing damage
Every morning I took the train to high street station
Doing homework on the train, what a fucked up situation
On the way back up hearing battle tapes
Through the underground, underneath the sky scrapes
Like harlem world battles on the zulu beat show
It's kool moe d vs. busy bee there's one you should know
Enough of that, I just want to give some respect due
M.C.A. grab the mic and the ma bell will connect you
Bob marley was a prophet for the freedom fight
&quot;if dancin' prays to the lord then I shall feel alright&quot;
I'm feeling good to play a little music
Tears running down my face 'cause I love to do it
And no one can stop this flow from flowing on
A flow master in disaster with a sound that's gone
I'll give a little shout out to my dad and mom
For bringing me into this world and so on

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Sabotage" track="5">I can't stand it I know you planned it
I'm gonna set it straight, this watergate
I can't stand rocking when I'm in here
Because your crystal ball ain't so crystal clear
So while you sit back and wonder why
I got this fucking thorn in my side
Oh my, it's a mirage
I'm tellin' y'all it's sabotage

So listen up 'cause you can't say nothin'
You'll shut me down with a push of your button?
But yo I'm out and i'm gone
I'll tell you now I keep it on and on

'cause what you see you might not get
And we can bet so don't you get souped yet
You're scheming on a thing that's a mirage
I'm trying to tell you now it's sabotage

Whyyy; our backs are now against the wall
Listen all of y'all it's a sabotage
Listen all of y'all it's a sabotage
Listen all of y'all it's a sabotage
Listen all of y'all it's a sabotage

I can't stand it, I know you planned it
But I'm gonna set it straight this watergate
But I can't stand rockin' when i'm in this place
Because I feel disgrace because you're all in my face
But make no mistakes and switch up my channel
I'm buddy rich when I fly off the handle
What could it be, it's a mirage
You're scheming on a thing - that's sabotage</song>
      <song title="Get It Together" track="6">1-2 1-2 keep it on
Listen to the shit because we kick it until dawn
Listen to the abstract got it going on
Listen to the ladies come on and let me spawn
All your eggs then you go up the river
Listen to the abstract that freaky nigger
I'm ad rock and I shock and i tick and i tock
And I can't stop with the body rock
See I've got heart like john starks
Hitting mad sparks
Pass me the mic
And I'll be rocking the whole park
I'm the m to the c to the a and it's a must
The rhymes that we bust on the topic on lust
And my moms is not butt, but fuck it
Let me get down to the rhythm
Yes I'm getting funky and i'm shooting all my jism
Like john holmes, the x-rated nigger
Listen to the shit 'cause I'm the ill figure
Nobody's getting any bigger than this

Get it together, get it together
Phone is ringing, oh my god
Get it together
See what's happening

Ad rock down with the ione
Listen to the shit because both of them is boney
Got to do it like this like chachi and joanie
Because she's the cheese and I'm the macaroni
So why all the fight and why all the fuss
Becasue I ain't got no dust
Yea, you know I'm getting silly
I've got a grandma hazel and a grandma tilly
Grand Royal prez And I'm Also A Member
Born on the cusp in the month of november
I do the patty duke in case you don't remember
Well, I freak a funky beat like the shit was in a blender
Well, I'm long gone word is born
Don't need a mother fucking fool telling me right from wrong
I don't think I'm slick nor do i play like i'm hard
But I'm a Drive The Lane Like I Was Evan Bernhard
And I've working on my game because life is taxing
Got to get it together and see what's happening

Get it together, get it together
Get it together
See what's happening

I go one two like my name was biz mark
But I had to do the shit just let me embark
On the lyric and the noun and the verb
Let's kick the shit off 'cause yo, I'm not the herb
Well, it's not the herb but the spice with the flavor to spare
The moog with the funk for your derriere
While we're on that topic, yes I like to mention
When it comes to boning I'm representing
Spacing, zoning, talkin' on the phone and
My brain is roaming and I don't know where it's going
Talking lots of shit a little tweaking on the weekend
I've got to get him by the reigns because I know that i'm freaking
Well, I'm a funky skull and i'm a scorpio
And when I get my flow i'm dr on the go
So q-tip, what you on the mic for
Because I had to talk about the times that i rhyme
And when M.C.s come in my face, I'm like mace
Because I back them off with the quills
Nigger 'cause I tell you, nigger 'cause i'll keep you under prills
Resting on nine one one sixteenth ave off the farmes boulevard
I'm from manhattan M.C.A.'s from brooklyn
Yea, M.C.A., your shit be cooking
Praying mantis on the court and I can't be beat
So, yo tip, what's up with the boot on your feet
I've got the timbos on the toes and this is how it goes
Oh one two, oh my god
One two, oh my god, I've got some shit
I've got the kung fu grip behind my green trap kit
Never ever ever smoking crack
Never ever ever fucking wack
I eat the fuckin' pineapple now &amp; laters
Listen to me now, don't listen to me later
Fuck it 'cause I know i didn't make it fuckin' rhyme for real
But, yo technically I'm as hard as steel
Gonna get it together, watch it, gonna get it together ma bell
I'm like ma bell, I've got the ill communications</song>
      <song title="The Update" track="7">I can hear the trumpets blowing screaming out the end of time
Look around and listen and you'll see every sign
The waters are polluted as the forests are cut down
Bombing and drilling deep below the ground
Check the prophecies from around the world
And look around now as it all unfurls
Look into yourself and see what goes on
Get a feeling in your heart of the right from wrong
Because the mother earth needs to be respected
Been far from too long that she's been neglected
Race against race, such a foolish waste
It's like cutting off your nose to spite your face
And at the end of the wars, what was the cost
It's clear that the earth was the one who lost
We are one with her as she is one with us
It's unreal how she is treated so unjust
As our planet grows smaller each and every day
Everyone affecting everyone in every way
We're all citizens of the world community
All here together and we're searching for unity
Over the years, I've grown and changed so much
Things I know now years ago, i couldn't touch
There are things I've done that i wouldn't do again
But I'm glad that i did 'cause i've learned from them
I just try to stay present right here, right now
No worries, no fears and without any doubts

It's about time &lt;I&gt;[x4]&lt;/i&gt;

'cause in these times, these changing times
A transition is occuring and I am not blind
As the pendlum swings a new age we enter
And with every swing, it draws closer to the center
Yes the storm before the calm and the wars that lead to love
Things must run their course so we push and we shove
But we're here to work it out in one way or another
To find a mutual respect for ourselves and one another
And the true key is a trust in self
For when I trust myself, i fear no one else
I took control of my life, just as anyone can
I want everyone to see it's in the palm of your hand
The past is gone, the future yet unborn
But right here and now is where it all goes on
I know we can fix it and it's not too late
I give respect to king and his nonviolent ways
I dream and I hope and i won't forget
Someday I'm going to visit on a free tibet
Someday I'm going to see us all joined as one
And it would be too bad to blow it up before we're done
'cause we long behind the rage learning from the pain
The love behind the tension like the sun behind the rain
I'm sending loving light to all that is
To all creation and the life we live
I'm not preaching bull shit, just speaking my mind
'cause I'm here now and it's about time</song>
      <song title="Futterman's Rule" track="8">&quot;when two are served, you may begin to eat&quot;

 Gene Futterman</song>
      <song title="Alright Hear This" track="9">Because I grab the microphone and i pick it up
And then I fuck it up and then i turn it in
And then I turn it out, got the body rockin' sound
And then you know I'm gonna get down and
Eat a scooby snack and take disco nap
Because I'm shopping at sears, 'cause i don't buy at the gap
Sending this one out to all the funky inspirations
Pretty purdie on the drums with the beat relations
Well, I'm working on rhymes, they're coming line by line
Trying to put what I feel into word and rhymes
I've got a feeling coming on, I've got to make some shit
A little something stupid, for the twisted and sick
Because I drive like a maniac on the streets
And I don't give fuck 'cause i've got the beats
Got my nuts swingin' from left to right and
Right to left and I'm death defying

Alright hear this
Alright hear this

I spin my fortune on a wheel like sajak
Here's the payback keep going strong like since the way back
I try to be myself but I lose track
'cause the shit gets complicated now I've got to get back
As we learn to breed love for one another
In these times of melying cultures
I give respect for what's been borrowed and lent
I know this music comes down from african descent
Because I don't need a magic potion
Let me talk about back field in motion
My girls got cheeks for weeks and I'm happy
You know I'm a sneak like my old grand pappy
I gotta give thanks to my man archie shep
For staying true to inspiration and I don't half step
So I kick out the jams and tell you who i am
And I talk to the people like les mccann

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

I ask god for a rhyme or two
A little something for the wise as well as the fool
A little something to affect a little taste of change
For the together and the strong as well as the dearanged
I'll do you right like bobby knight
And then I'm rapping on the mic to the broadway light
Stomp my hands, I clap my feet and
I'm bugging off yusef lateef
I got a match to my ass and I'm a keep it lit
I need to get some cash, call my accountant britt
I'm rushing around town taking care of my functions
Always got one more thing so forget about function
We create this world and the problems go on
Create our lives and the things that go wrong
So to the deaf, the blind, look around and listen
To what it is you want and for what you're wishing

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Flute Loop" track="10">Moon Me!

So, just sit back and max and relax
Off tracks that I kick, come on and give it up
'causei get funky like diaper rash
And you know I'm mad spunky and i'm making cash
I've got sex rhymes like victoria's got secrets
To all you porne peepers who are trying to peep this
I'm like al goldstein, I'm all about screwing
Lead my team to sixty wins like my man pat ewing
Like getting shot out the barrel of a wave
Like virgin pow on the peaks of A.K.
Like a sound that to the depths of the soul
Well that's the feeling that I make my goal

A little wine with my dinner so I'm in the grape ape
I feel like a winner when I make a mix tape
Because I get ill when i'm on the pause button
And I get my fill and you can't say nothing
More soul on this train then don cornelious
Got the mad subwoofer pumping bass for your anus
Just getting on the mic at the monthly function
Wires hitting switches connecting at the junction
Perlman's got beats and it ain't no secret
Dante found his shit but you know he freaked it
And so the story goes on and on
Down in S.D. 50 'till early morning</song>
      <song title="Do It" track="11">&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Like the black birds I'm a do it fluid
Building rhymes like buildings, like a stonehenge druid
Step up and get enlightened, educating my mind
I play the tape forward, it's not time to rewind
Step inside the mother fucker and I get my flow on
Amalgamating styles so I've got something to grow on
Season's change when it comes their time
Falls brings the winter and on back to springtime
Well, it's the king ad rock and that's who I am
Listen all of y'all I'm not the son of sam
'cause I'm thin and i don't grin
But check it out people 'cause I love to go and swim
Caught up on the phone fiber optic distraction
Information super highway got the brain contraction
I'm the kung fu master vs. the sumo wrestler
Got the beats in manhatten you can hear in westchester
Well, my mother was born out in coney island
Raised on the L.E.S. manhatten island
My dad camo out from detroit and they had me
And back on through ellis island goes through the family tree
Well, I'm a six point seven on the richter scale
I've got rhymes gallot and then I never fail
Like gravy to potatos, luke to darth vader
I'm a souped up sucker and I'll see you all later

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

You see me coming down the block with the funky cuts
You say mike D. and I say mic these nuts
I've got attractions like I'm elvis costello
Adam yauch grab the mic 'cause you know you're my mellow
Well when I get it into the zone
I'm gonna take it to a place where it's all one
My shit is on and the rhyme style's kicking
My brain is flowing honest like abe lincoln
'cause I'm the fuckin' rythm ace with the rhyme selection
Listen all y'all I rap with perfection
Because I got the mother fuckin' old school flavor
That you savor so watch your behavior
Talking other dimensions, levels higher
Why did billy joel say we didn't start the fire
Take you to another realm, another level
I've got the funky rhymes but I'm not the funky devil
I step from minute to minute, lifetime to lifetime
Step from stage to stage to see it all unwind
Slowly but surely I seek to find my mind
And every wall that I face is of my own desig
Glendale boulevard boulevard
Glendale boulevard is where I'm at
It's where I'm at, where i live
Check it out because my head is like a siv
And we turn it out

&lt;i&gt;[Chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Heart Attack Man" track="12">Drink a six pack and then you play som ball
Walking down the stairs and then he starts to fall
Add on two joints and then he starts to sweat
Two hundred seventy five punds that you can't forget

Heart attack, heart attack man
Spend all your money on your health insurance plan
Heart attack, heart attack man
Keep on getting bigger because you know that you can

Why do you force yourself on top of that girl
Laugh with all your buddies because it's a man's man's world
Someday that shit will come back to you
You've been throwing your weight around and
Your shit is through

Heart attack, heart attack man
Going nowhere, got no master plan
Heart attack, heart attack man
Heart Attack

Weighs in at two seventy five
Yeh my man is lucky to be alive
Smokin' and drinkin' too
My man the heart attack man is gonna be running over you
Got no god damn respect
Had to put the big big bitch-ass in check

Heart attack, heart attack man
Lungs full of tar and a stomach full of spam
Heart attack, heart attack man
Time to change your ways heart attack man

What do we know about partying or anything else?</song>
      <song title="The Scoop" track="13">I Don't get Blind I Don't Drink Wine
I took a sledge hammer and I broke my nine
Because my record is mine, word is born I rhyme
And everey day I write the book down line by line
I'm feeling good when I do it like this
So come on and turn it up because you can't resist
Because I'm back with another track wich you lack
'cause things is wack and that's a fact
Because I'm on time, you're shouting rewind
You know it's ad rock that's blowing your mind
My shit is rough and you know it is so damn tough
I'm getting intense, not talking nonsese
I made up my mind, not sitting on the fence
I don't always know the right from the wrong
I do my best to figure it out and work it out in the long
I try to do a lot more than I can chew
Balance out my ambition's what I've got to do

Because you hide in broad day light, a parasite
A hypocrite, you take a peek quick
You turn your nose up, you think you're high up
You play it real safe and now your shit's fake
I seen you hawking and then you clock my style
And then you try to play it off like you think you're wild
D.I.Y. that means do it yourself
I don't sit around waiting for someone's help
Don't sit back and say good enough
Keep on striving, reinventing but keeping it off
The Cuff
So kick the level up cuhootnified
Mackadocius vibes positively fortified
I'm throwing rhymes down kicking them downtown
Traveling high speed through the underground
I kick it free style, make it worth your while
I've got shelves of rhymes that I keep on file
I'm feeling good now back home again
New york city is the city that I feel at home in

A blast from the grasshoff awhile it's been
Stepping into the future again
I'm straight from the 88 to 93 to 94, I'm out the door
Step into the party with the fila fresh gear
People looking at me like I was david koresh here
Kicking rhymes from the heart 'cause that's where I'm at
Fuck the bullshit, be it far from me to pop that
In the search for truth, I go a lot of ways
There's not a lot of peace, that I find these days
I try to stay cool, I try to stay calm
But my life is getting hectic like a smoke bomb
So I'll say it like the group huggy bear
There's a boy-grrrl revolution of wich you should be aware
You can't dis me, it ain't worth it, b
You put yourself down and you don't even see
Cause I don't play that, i know who i am
For a minute, I did but now i'm back again
I'm feeling strong see, trust myself g
Well I stopped smoking cheeba
And that was part of the key
We've got fire, we need water
There ain't no water so I guess i ought to
Leave you broke in a comatose state of mind
And I'm blind and i'm working overtime, so check it
I keep my rhymes in a little black book
And I know you want to take another look</song>
      <song title="Bodhisattva Vow" track="14">As I develop the awakening mind i praise the buddha as they shine
I bow before you as I travel my path to join your ranks,
I make my full time task
For the sake of all beings I seek
The enlighted mind that I know i'll reap
Respect to shantideva and all the others
Who brought down the darma for sisters and brothers
I give thanks for this world as a place to learn
And for this human body that I know i've earned
And my deepest thanks to all sentient beings
For without them there would be no place to learn what I'm seeing
There's nothing here that's not been said before
But I put it down now so i'll be sure
To solidify my own views and I'll be glad if it helps
Anyone else out too

If others disrespect me or give me flack
I'll stop and think before I react 
Knowing that they're going through insecure stages
I'll take the opportunity to exercise patience
I'll see it as a chance to help the other person
Nip it in the bud before it can worsen
A change for me to be strong and sure
As I think on the buddhas who have come before
As I praise and respect the good they've done
Knowing only love can conquer in every situation
We need other people in order to create
The circumstances for the learning that we're here to generate
Situations that bring up our deepest fears
So we can work to release them until they're cleared
Therefore, it only makes sense
To thank our enemies despite their intent

The bodhisattva path is one of power and strength
A strength from within to go the length
Seeing others are as important as myself
I strive for a happiness of mental wealth
With the interconnectedness that we share as one
Every action that we take affects everyone
So in deciding for what a situation calls
There is a path for the good for all
I try to make my every action for that highest good
With the altruistic wish to achive buddhahood
So I pledge here before everyone who's listening
To try to make my every action for the good of all beings
For the rest of my lifetimes and even beyond
I vow to do my best to do no harm
And in times of doubt I can think on the dharma
And the enlightened ones who've graduated samsara</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Licensed To Ill" year="1986">
      <song title="Rhymin &amp; Stealin" track="1">Because mutiny on the bounty's what we're all about
I'm gonna board your ship and turn it on out
No soft sucker with a parrot on his shoulder
'Cause I'm bad gettin' bolder - cold getting colder
Terrorizing suckers on the seven seas
And if you've got beef - you'll get capped in the knees
We got sixteen men on a dead man's chest
And I shot those suckers and I'll shoot the rest

&lt;i&gt;[chorus]&lt;/i&gt;
 Most illingest b-boy - I got that feeling
Cause I am most ill and I'm rhymin' and stealin'

Snatching gold chains - vicking pieces of eight
I got your money and your honey and the fly name plate
We got wenches on the benches - and bitties with titties
Housing all girlies from city to city
One for all and all for one
Taking out M.C.'s with a big shotgun
All for one and one for all
Because the beastie boys have gone A.W.O.L.
Friggin' in the riggin' and cuttin' your throat
Big biting suckers getting thrown in the moat
We got maidens and wenches - man they're on the ace
Captain Bly is gonna die when we break his face

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Ali Baba and the forty thieves

Torching and crakin' and rhymin' and stealin'
Robbin' and raping - busting two in the ceiling
I'm wheeling' - I'm dealin' - i'm drinking, not thinking
Never cower, never shower - and I'm always stinking
Ho ho ho and a pint of Brass Monkey
And when my girlie shakes her hips - she sure gets funky
Skirt chasing, free basing - killing every village
We drink and rob and rhyme and pillage

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

I've been drinking my rum - a Def son of a gun
I fought the law and I cold won
Black Beard's weak - Moby Dick's on the tick
'Cause I pull out the jammy and squeeze off six
My pistol is loaded - I shot Betty Crocker
Deliver colonel sanders down to davey jones' locker
Rhymin' and stealin' in a drunken state
And I'll be rockin' my rhymes all the way to Hell's gate

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="The New Style" track="2">And on the cool check in
Center stage on the mic
And we're puttin' it on wax
It's the new style

Four and three and two and one What up!
And when I'm on the mic - the suckers run (word!)
Down with adrock and mike D. and you ain't
And I got more juice than Picasso got paint
Got rhymes that are rough and rhymes that are slick
I'm not surprised you're on my dick
B-E-A-S-T-I-E, what up Mike D.
Ah yeah, that's me
I got franks and pork and beans
Always bust the new routines
I get it - I got it, I know it's good
The rhymes I write - you wish you would 
I'm never in training - my voice is not straining
People always biting and I'm sick of complaining
So I went into the locker room during classes
Bust into your locker and I smashed your glasses
You're from secausus - I'm from manhattan
You're jealous of me because your girlfriend is cattin'

There it is - kick it!!!

Father to many - married to none
And in case you're unaware I carry a gun
Stepped into the party - the place was over packed
Saw the kid that dissed my homey and shot him in the back
I had to get a beeper 'cause my phone is tapped
You better keep your mouth shut 'cause I'm fully strapped
I got money in the bank - I can still get high
That's why your girlfriend thinks that I'm so fly
I've got money and juice - twin sisters in my bed
Their father had envy so I shot him in the head
If I played guitar I'd be Jimmy Page
The girlie's I like are underage check it!
Girls with boyfriends are the kind I like
I'll steal your honey like I stole your bike
Your father - he's jealous 'cause I'm making that green
I've got the girlie's numbers from the places I been

There it is - kick it!!!

You wanna know why - because I'm
October 31st - that is my date of birth
I got to the party and I did the Smurf
Taxing all females from coast to coast
And when I get my fill i'm chilly most
We rag-tag girlies back at the hotel
And then we all switch places when I ring the bell
I chill at White Castle 'cause it's the best
But I'm fly at Fat Burger when I way out west
K-I-N-G-A-D whammy
All the fly ladies are on my jammy
Went to the prom - wore the fly blue rental
Got six girlies in my Lincoln Continental
Met this girl at the party and she started to flirt
I told her some rhymes and she pulled up her skirt
Spent some bank - I got a high powered jumbo
Rolled up a wooly and I watched Colombo

Let me clear my throat - Kick it over here baby pop
And let all the fly skimmies, feel the beat...mmm drop

Coolin' on the corner on a hot summers day
Just me, my posse and M.C.A.
A lot of beer - a lot of girls - and a lot of cursing
Twenty-two automatic on my person
Got my hand in my pocket and my finger's on the trigger
My posse's gettin' big - and my posse's gettin' bigger
Some voices got treble - some voices got bass
We got the kind of voices that are in your face
Like the bun to the burger - like the burger to the bun
Like the cherry to the apple - to the peach to the plum
I'm the king of the Ave. - and I'm the king of the block
I'm M.C.A. - and I'm the king adrock
I'm mike D. - I got all the fly juice
On the checkin' at the party on the forty deuce
Walking down the block with the fresh fly threads
Beastie Boys fly the biggest heads</song>
      <song title="She's Crafty" track="3">Well this girl came up to me - she says she's new in town
But the crew been said they seen her around
I thought they were right but I didn't wanna know
The girlie was Def and she wanted to go
I think her name is Lucy but they all call Loose
I think I thought i seen her on eighth and forty-deuce
The next think she said, &quot;My place or yours?
Let's kick some bass behind closed doors!&quot;
We got into the cab - the cab driver said
He recognized my girlie from the back of her head
He said a little something about tip to base
So I made him stop the cab to get out of the place
I shouldn't have looked back man I'll always regret it
Something's going on and I'll probably never get it
She was crying like a baby - stupid dumb
It's just too bad that girl's a bum

She's crafty - she's gets around
She's crafty - she's always down
She's crafty - she's got a gripe
She's crafty - and she's just my type
She's crafty

I spent my last dollar to by a Sabrett
When I seen this girl I could never forget
Now I like nothing better than a pretty girl smile
And I haven't seen a smile that pretty in a while
The girl came up to me she said she loved the show
Asked her to come home and she couldn't say, &quot;No!&quot;
We got the crib - there's Adam and D.
We didn't say a word - they just stared at me
I said, &quot;I don't know her just met her tonight.&quot;
And Adrock started hiding everything in sight
D. pulled me over said, &quot;Hide your gold,
The girl is crafty like ice is cold!&quot;
The girl is crafty - she knows all the moves
I started playing records - she knew all the grooves
He thought she was a thief - and D. was right
But I just figured she'd spend the night
When I woke up late in the afternoon
She had taken all the things from inside his room
I found myself naked in the middle of the floor
She had taken the bed and the chest of drawers
The mirror, the TV, the guitar cord
My remote control and my old skateboard
She robbed us blind - she took all we owned
And the boys blamed me for bringing her home

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Posse In Effect" track="4">Yes, yes, y'all - you don't stop
You keep it on - and shockin' the place
Well I'm M.C.A. - i got nothing to prove
Pay attention - my intention is to bust a move
I drink quarts and cans and bottles and sixes
Between the turntables keep the vodka and the mixes
I'm mike D. - I got the deuces wild
A list of girlies numbers that I've dialed
I do the Smurf, the Popeye, and the Jerry Lewis
I like bullwinkle but I don't like moose
I'm schoolin' in the boys' room - coolin' by the locker
All the girls in class know that I'm the cool rocker
Punk in the hall - man I should of oughtta hit him
Had the fresh rhymes and the kid cold bite 'em
Smokin' in the boys room is what I do best
While you were at a party - your girlfriend fessed
I keep a pistol in my pocket so you better be cautious
Fly around the world - but it makes me nauseous
Mike D.'s day off everyday of the week
I got to the party - and I did the freak
I got a girl in the Castle and one in the pagoda
You know I got rhymes like abe vigoda
I'm a def manhattan killer - a rhyme driller
A mike in my hand and a mouth full of Miller
I got a hat not a visor - I drink Budweiser
The turntables - up on the drum riser
The needle's in the groove and the vinyl's on the platter
I know that I'm fly man there's no need to flatter
I travel around the globe - it's keeping girlies dizzy
My name's mike D. - now watch me get busy y'all

You're a fake wearin' sucker whose gold got rusted
Cheaper than a hot dog with no mustard
You tried to steal my fresh and you got cold busted
Because your crew's all soft and I'm disgusted
I'm from downtown from the city of Manhattan
I got a lotta girlies and not one's cattin'
My posse's in effect and we're doin' the do
And we got more rhymes than your damn crew
Caught you poppin' that weak and you must of been dusted
Stuck you head in the toilet and stone cold flushed it
Word.</song>
      <song title="Slow Ride" track="5">They got a committee to get me off the block
'Cause I say my rhymes loud and I say 'em nonstop
Because being bad news is what we're all about
We went to White Castle and we got thrown out
I got my boy Mike D. - I got the King Adrock I got the jammy with the ammo inside my sock
I shot homeboy but the bullet was a dud
So I reached in the Miller cooler - grabbed a cool Bud

Slow riding, gun hidin' on the go
I'm fly like an eagle and I drink Old Crow
I'm the king of the classroom - coolin' in the back
My teacher had beef so I gave her a smack
She chased me out of class she was strapped with a ruler
Went to the bathroom - rolled myself a wooler
With bottle in hand at the microphone stand
A. yo homeboy - what you drinkin' man

I got money, I got juice
I got to the party and I got loose
I got rhythms, I got rhymes
I got the girlies with the Def behinds
I got ill, I got busted
I got dust and I got dusted
I got gold, I got funky
I got the new dance they call the Brass Monkey

Because I'm hard hittin' always biten cool as hell
I got trees on my mirror so my car won't smell
Sittin' around the house gettin' high and watchin' tube
Eating Colonel's chicken drinkin' Heineken brew
I'm a gangster, I'm a prankster I'm the king of the Ave.
I'm hated, confrontated for the juice that I have
All the fly ladies are making a fuss
But I can't pay attention 'cause I'm on that dust</song>
      <song title="Girls" track="6">Girls, all I really want is girls
And in the morning it's girls
Cause in the evening it's girls

I like the way that they walk
And it's chill to hear them talk
And I can always make them smile
From white castle to the nile

Back in the day
There was this girl around the way
She liked by home-piece M.C.A.
He said he would not give her play
I asked him, &quot;Please?&quot; he said, &quot;You may.&quot;
Her pants were tight and that's ok
If she would dance I would D.J.
We took a walk down to the bay

I hope she'll say, &quot;Hey me and you should hit the hay!&quot;
I asked her out she said, &quot;No way!&quot;
I should have probably guessed their gay
So I broke North with no delay
I heard she moved real far away
That was two years ago this May
I seen her just the other day
Jockin' mike D. to my dismay

Girls - to do the dishes
Girls - to clean up my room
Girls - to do the laundry
Girls - and in the bathroom
Girls, that's all I really want is girls
Two at a time I want girls
With new wave hairdos I want girls
I ought to whip out my girls, girls, girls, girls, girls!</song>
      <song title="Fight For Your Right" track="7">Kick it! 

You wake up late for school man you don't wanna go
You ask you mom, &quot;Please?&quot; but she still says, &quot;No!&quot;
You missed two classes and no homework
But your teacher preaches class like you're some kind of jerk

You gotta fight for your right to party

You pops caught you smoking and he said, &quot;No way!&quot;
That hypocrite smokes two packs a day
Man, living at home is such a drag
Now your mom threw away your best porno mag Bust it!

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Don't step out of this house if that's the clothes you're gonna wear
I'll kick you out of my home if you don't cut that hair
Your mom busted in and said, &quot;What's that noise?&quot;
Aw, mom you're just jealous it's the Beastie Boys!

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="No Sleep 'Til Brooklyn" track="8">No sleep 'til - brooklyn

Foot on the pedal never ever false metal
Engine running hotter than a boiling kettle
My job's ain't a job it's a damn good time
City to city I'm running my rhymes
On location touring around the nation
Beastie Boys always on vacation
Itchy trigger finger but a stable turntable
I do what I do best because I'm illing and able
Ain't no faking your money I'm taking
Going coast to coast watching all the girlies shaking
While you're at the job working nine to five
The beastie boys at the garden cold kickin' it live

No sleep 'til -

Another plane another train
Another bottle in the brain
Another girl another fight
Another drive all night
Our manager's crazy he always smokes dust
He's got his own room at the back of the bus
Tour around the world you rock around the clock
Plane to hotel girls on the jock
We're thrashing hotels like it's going out of style
Getting paid along the way cause it's worth your while
Four on the floor Adrock's out the door
M.C.A.'s in the back because he's skeezin' with a whore
We got a safe in the trunk with money in a stack
With dice in the front and Brooklyn's in the back

No sleep 'til -

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Ain't seen the light since we started this band
M.C.A. get on the mic my man
Born and bred Brooklyn U.S.A.
They all me Adam Yauch but I'm M.C.A.
Like a lemon to a lime a lime to a lemon
I sip the def ale with all the fly women
Got limos, arena, TV shows
Autograph pictures and classy hos
Step off homes get out of my way
Taxing little girlies form here to L.A.
Waking up before I get to sleep
Cause I'll be rocking this party eight days a week

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Paul Revere" track="9">Now here's a little story I've got to tell
About three bad brothers you know so well
It started way back in history
With adrock, M.C.A., and me - mike D.
Been had a little horsy named Paul Revere
Just me and my horsy and a quart of beer
Riding across the land, kicking up sand
Sheriff's posse on my tail cause I'm in demand
One lonely beastie I be
All by myself without nobody
The sun is beating down on my baseball hat
The air is gettin' hot the beer is getting flat
Lookin' for a girl I ran into a guy
His name is M.C.A., I said, &quot;Howdy&quot; he said, &quot;Hi&quot;

He told a little story that sounded well rehearsed
Four days on the run and that he's dying of thirst
The brew was in my hand and he was on my tip
His voice was hoarse, his throat was dry he asked me for a sip
He said, &quot;can I get some?&quot;
I said, &quot;you can't get none!&quot;
Had a chance to run
He pulled out his shotgun
He was quick on the draw I thought I'd be dead
He put the gun to my head and this is what he said,

&quot;Now my name is M.C.A. I've got a license to kill
I think you know what time it is it's time to get ill
Now what do we have here an outlaw and his beer
I run this land, you understand I make myself clear.&quot;
We stepped into the wind he had a gun, I had a grin
You think this story's over but it's ready to begin

&quot;Now I got the gun you got the brew
You got two choices of what you can do
It's not a tough decision as you can see
I can blow you away or you can ride with me&quot; I said, I'll ride with you if you can get me to the border
The sheriff's after me for what I did to his daughter
I did it like this, I did it like that
I did it with a whiffleball bat
So I'm on the run the cop's got my gun
And right about now it's time to have some fun
The king adrock that is my name
And I know the fly spot where they got the champagne.&quot;
We rode for six hours then we hit the spot
The beat was a bumping and the girlies was hot
This dude was staring like he knows who we are
We took the empty spot next to him at the bar
M.C.A. said, &quot;yo, you know this kid?&quot;
I said, &quot;I didn'T.&quot; but i know he did
The kid said, &quot;Get ready cause this ain't funny
My name's mike D. and I'm about to get money.&quot;
Pulled out the jammy aimed it at the sky
He yelled, &quot;stick 'em up!&quot; and let two fly
Hands went up and people hit the floor
He wasted two kids that ran for the door
&quot;I'm mike D. and i get respect
Your cash and your jewelry is what I expect&quot;
M.C.A. was with it and he's my ace
So I grabbed the piano player and I punched him in the face
The piano player's out the music stopped
His boy had beef and he got dropped
Mike D. grabbed the money M.C.A. snatched the gold
I grabbed two girlies and a beer that's cold.</song>
      <song title="Hold It Now - Hit It!" track="10">Now I chill real ill when I start to chill
When I fill my pockets with a knot of dollar bills
Sipping pints of ale out the window sill
When I get my fill I'm chilly chill
Now I just got home because I'm out on bail
What's the time? it's time to buy ale
Peter eater parking meter all of the time
If I run out of ale it's Thunderbird wine
Miller drinking chicken eating dress so fly
I got friends in high places that are keeping me high
Down with mike D. and it ain't no hassle
Got the ladies of the eighties from here to White Castle

Hold it now - hit it!

M.C. adam yauch in the place to be
And all the girls are on me cause I'm down with Mike D.
I'm down with Mike D. and it ain't no baloney
For real, not phony &quot;O.E.&quot; and Rice-a-Roni
I come out at night 'cause I sleep all day
And I'm the King Adrock and he's M.C.A.
Well I'm cruising, I'm bruising I'm never ever losing
I'm in my car I'm going far and dust is what I'm using
Around the way is where I'm from
And I'm from Manhattan and I'm not a bum
Because you're pud-slapping, ball-flapping - got that juice
My name's mike D. and I can do that jerry lewis

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Hip-hop, body rockin' doing the do
Beer drinking, breath stinking, sniffing glue
Belly flipping, always illing, busting caps
My name's mike D. and I write my own snaps
I'm a peep-show seeking on the forty-deuce
I'm a killer at large and I'm on the loose
Pistol packing, monkey drinking, no money bum
I come from Brooklyn 'cause that's where I'm from
Cheap-skate, perpetrating - money hungry jerk
Everyday I drink a &quot;O.E.&quot; and I don't go to work
You drippy nose knuckle-head - you're we behind the ears
You like men - and we like beer.

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

King of the Ave. with the Def female
You're rhyming and stealin' with the freshest ale
Cooling at the crib watching my TV
Ed norton - ted knight - and mr. ed
Pump it up homeboy just don't stop
Chef Boy-ar-dee cooling on the pot
I take no slack cause I got the knack
And I'm never dusting out cause I torch that crack
The king adrock that is my name
And you're drinking Moet we got the champagne
A quarter dropping going shopping buying wigs
Surgeon general cut professor D.J. Thigs

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Brass Monkey" track="11">Brass monkey - that funky monkey
Brass Monkey junkie
That funky monkey

Got this dance that's more than real
Drink brass monkey here's how you feel
Put your left leg down your right leg up
Tilt your head back let's finish the cup
M.C.A. with the bottle D. rocks the can
Adrock gets nice with Charlie Chan
We're offered moet we don't mind chivas
Wherever we go with bring the Monkey with us
Adrock drinks three Mike D. is D.
Double R. foots the bill most definitely
I drink brass monkey and I rock well
I got a Castle in Brooklyn that's where I dwell

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Cause I drink it anytime and anyplace
When it's time to get ill I pour it on my face
Monkey tastes def when you pour it on ice
Come on y'all it's time to get nice
Coolin' by the lockers getting kind of funky
Me and the crew we're drinking Brass Monkey
This girl walked by she gave me the eye
I reached in the locker grabbed the Spanish Fly
I put it with the Monkey mixed it in the cup
Went over to the girl, &quot;Yo baby, what's up?&quot;
I offered her a sip the girl she gave me lip
It did begin the stuff wore in and now she's on my tip

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

Step up to the bar put the girl down
She takes a big gulp and slaps it around
Take a sip - you can do it - you get right to it
We had a case in the place and we went right through it
You got a dry Martini thinking you're cool
I'll take your place at the bar I smack you off your stool
I'll down a '40 dog&quot; in a single gulp
And if you got beef you'll get beat to a pulp
Monkey and parties and reelin' and rockin'
Def, def - girls, girls - all y'all jockin'
The song and dance keeping you in a trance
If you don't buy my record I got my advance
I drink it - I think it - I see it - I be it
I love brass monkey but I won't give D. it
We got the bottle you got the cup
Come on everybody let's get ffffff

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Slow And Low" track="12">Let it flow - let yourself go
Slow and low - that is the tempo

It's never old school all brand new
So everybody catch the bugaloo flu
Not like a fever not like a cold
The beats are clear the rhymes are bold
So don't see a doctor or see a nurse
Just listen to the music first things first
First of all get off the wall
It's time to party so have a ball
We slowed it on down so get the hell up
Like a volcano I'll erupt
We got determination - bass and highs
White Castle fries only come in one size
What you see is what you get
And you ain't seen nothing yet

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

I do not sing but I make a Def song
You could live your whole life and I hope you live long
On the gong show we won't get gonged
We're the beastie boys not cheech and chong
Strong as an ox fresh out the box
The crowd is so live they're coming in flocks
And when we go on the crowd goes off
It's all hard rock there's nothing soft

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

We don't only rock the house but we'll house we rock
We don't stroll but we roll straight to the top
M.C.A., adrock, mike D. makes three
And we can do it like this in the place to be
When I'm recorded you'll be rewarded
I know my song is Def 'cause you all applauded
Not P.C.P. or L.S.D. just me Mike D. in the place to be
This is not for free you must pay a fee
Cash on delivery like a C.O.D.

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;

The beat is slow in order to dance
I wanna hear I dos and no I can'ts
First you move your legs and then your arms
It's not fast and nervous this dance is calm
It's truly stable and you ought to be able
To dance to the record when it's on the turntable

&lt;i&gt;[repeat chorus]&lt;/i&gt;</song>
      <song title="Time To Get Ill" track="13">I'm not the type of person who likes to waste my time
And when I'm on the mic i just say my rhymes
Because I'm out on bail the check is in the mail
They can sentence me to life but I won't go to jail
I'm cool calm collected from class I was ejected
Just me, mike D., and M.C.A. we're rarely disrespected
I got all the time that I need to kill
What's the time? it's time to get ill

You been fully captivated by that funky ass bass
Your girlfriend screams when M.C.A.'s in the place
He stumbles in the room with the Chivas in his hand
Cold chillin' on the spot at the microphone stand
I'd have the pedal to the metal if I had a car
But I'm chiller with the Miller cold coolin' at the bar
I can drink a quart of Monkey and still stand still
What's the time? it's time to get ill

Went outside my house I went down to the deli
I spent my last dime to refill my fat belly
I got rhymes galime I got rhymes galilla
And I got more rhymes than Phillis Diller
M.C.A. takes a stand man you're in command
Homeboy, turn it out and don't give a damn
My name is M.C.A. I've got a license to kill
What's the time? it's time to get ill

Riding down the block with my box in my hand
Today I feel like chillin' just as chill as I can
Coolin' on the corner with a forty of O.E.
'Cause me and M.C.A. we're down with Mike D.
When I run a jam I don't give a damn
When I'm throwing bass I say, &quot;Thank you ma'am.&quot;
Fuel injected, rhyme connected running things
I'm the king adrock and I'm the king of all kings
I'm looking for a spot things are gettin' hot
I'm M.C.A., I'm here to stay and you sir, are not
Oh no, it could not be it's such a sight to see
It's such a trip you're on my tip so listen to Mike D.
My work is my play cause I'm playing when I work
My name's mike D., as you can see and I can dot the jerk
M.C.A., adrock, mike D. - it's chill
What's the time? it's time to get ill</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Paul's Boutique" year="1989">
      <song title="Shake Your Rump" track="1">Now I rock a house party at the drop of a hat
I beat a biter down with an aluminum bat
a lot of people they be Jonesin' just to hear me rock the mic
they'll be staring at the radio
staying up all night
so like a pimp I'm pimpin'
I got a boat to eat shrimp in
Nothing wrong with my leg just B-boy limpin'
Got arrested at the Mardi Gras for jumping on a float
My man mca's got a beard like a billy goat
oowah oowah is my disco call
Mca hu-huh I'm gettin' rope y'all
Routines I bust rhymes I write
And I'll be busting routines and rhymes all night
Like eating burgers or chicken or you'll be picking your nose
I'm on time homie that's how it goes
You heard my style I think you missed the point
it's the joint

Mike d yeah?with your bad self running things
What's up with your bad breath onion rings
Well I'm mike d and i'm back from the dead
Chillin' at the beaches down at Club Med
Make another record 'cause the people they want more of this
Suckers they be saying they can take out Adam Horovitz
Hurricane you got clout
Other DJ's he'll take your head out
A puppet on a string I'm paid to sing or rhyme
Or do my thing I'm
In a lava lamp inside my brain hotel
I might be peakin' or freakin' but I rock well
The patty duke the wrench and then I bust the tango
Got more rhymes than Jamaica got Mango Kangols
I got the peg leg at the end of my stump
Shake your rump

Full Clout y'all
Full Clout y'all
And when the mic is in my mouth I turn it out y'all
Full Clout

Never been dumped 'cause I'm the most mackinest
Never been jumped 'cause I'm known the most packinest
Yeah we've got beef chief
We're knocking out teeth chief
And if you don't believe us you should question your belief Keith
Like Sam the butcher bringing Alice the meat
Like fred flintstone driving around with bald feet
Should I have another sip no skip it
In the back of the ride and bust with the whippet
Rope a dope dookies all around the neck
Whoo ha got them all in check
Running from the law the press and the parents
Is your name Michael Diamond?
No mine's clarence
From downtown manhattan the village
My style is wild and you know that it still is
Disco bag schlepping and you're doing the bump
Shake your rump</song>
      <song title="Johnny Ryall" track="2">Johnny Ryall is the bum on my stoop
I gave him fifty cents to buy some soup
He knows the time with the fresh Gucci watch
He's even more over than the mayor Ed Koch
Washing windows on the Bowery at a quarter to four
'Cause he ain't gonna work on Maggie's farm no more
Living on borrowed time and borrowed money
Sleepin' on the street there ain't a damn thing funny
Hand me down food and hand me down clothes
A rockabilly past of which nobody knows
Makes his home all over the place
He goes to sleep by falling down on his face
Sometimes known as the leader of the homeless
Sometimes drunk and he's always phoneless
Sleepin' on the street in a cardboard box
He's better off drinkin' than smokin' the rocks
Johnny ryall, johnny ryall

He drinks where he lies
He's covered with flies
He's got the hand me down Pumas and the tie dyes
Go upstate and get your head together
Thunderbird is the word and you're light as a feather
Detox at the flop house no booze allowed
Remember the good old days with the rockabilly crowd
Memphis is where he's from
He lives in the street but he's no bum
A rockabilly star from the days of old
He used to have teeth all filled with gold
A platinum voice but only gold records
On the bass was boots on the drums was checkers
Luis Vuitton with the Gucci guitar
Johnny Ryall
Who do you think you are
Johnny ryall, johnny ryall

Donald trump donald tramp living in the men's shelter
Wonder Bread bag shoes and singing Helter Skelter
He asks for a dollar you know what it's for
Bottle after bottle he'll always need more
He's no less important than you working class stiffs
Drinks a lot of liquor but he don't drink piss
Paid his dues playing the blues
He claims that he wrote the Blue Suede Shoes
Elvis shaved his head when he went into the army
That's right y'all his name is
Johnny
Johnny ryall, johnny ryall</song>
      <song title="Egg Man" track="3">I looked out the window and seen his bald head
I ran to the fridge and pulled out an egg
Scoped him with my scopes he had no hair
Launched that shot and he was caught out there
Saw the convertible driving by
Loaded up the slingshot and let one fly
He went for his to find he didn't have one
Put him in check correct with my egg gun
The egg a symbol of life
Go inside your house and bust out your wife
Pulled out the jammy he thought it was a joke
The trigger I pulled his face the yoke
Reached in his pocket took all his cash
Left my man standing with an egg moustache
Suckers they come a dime a dozen
And when I say dozen you know what i'm talking about boyee

Yeh, that's right, I'm the Egg Man
Driving around, king of the town
Always got my windows rolled down
You know, I'm the egg man

Once upon a time
Humpty Dumpty was a big fat egg
He was playing the wall and then he broke his leg
Tossed it out the window three minutes hot
Hit the rastaman he said bloodclot
Which came first the chicken or the egg
I egged the chicken then I ate his leg
Riding the trains in between cars
When I pull out the station you're gonna get yours
Drive by eggings plaguing L.A.
Yo they just got my little cousin ese
Sometimes hard boiled sometimes runny
It comes from a chicken not a bunny dummy
People laugh it's no joke
My name's yauch and I'm throwing the yoke
Now they got me in a cell but I don't care
It was then that I caught catching people out there

Up on the roof, in my car
Up all night, I'm pulling through signs like Dolomite
The mack, I'm the egg man
Taxi driver, I'm the egg man

We all dressed in black we snuck up around the back
We began to attack the eggs did crack on Haze's back
Sam I am down with the program
Green eggs and ham Yosemite Sam
Come Halloween you know I come strapped
I throw it at a sucker K-pap
You made the mistake you judge a man by his race
You go through life with egg on your face
You woke up in the morning with a peculiar feeling
You looked up and saw egg dripping from the ceiling
Families puck rocks the businessman
I'll dog anybody with an egg in my hand
Not like the crack that you put in a pipe
But crack on your forehead here's a towel now wipe</song>
      <song title="High Plains Drifter" track="4">Cause I'm the High Plains Drifter,
And I'm a drifter
The hight plains drifter,
And I'm a drifter
They can't catch me never gonna find me
They're never gonna know that I'm the High Plains Drifter

Pulled over to the river to take a rest
Pulled out a pair of pliers and pulled the bullet out of my chest
Fear and loathing across the country listening to my 8 track
I Reached behind the seat and grabbed a Kool from the pack
Long distance from my girl and I'm talking on the cellular
She said that she was sorry and I said yeah the hell you were
Check my rear view mirror check the gold tooth display
Check out the odometer and I was on my way
Cause I'm a high plains drifter the best that you can get
A strapped shoplifter a pirate on cassette
Bust a travis bickle when I feel that i'm getting pushed
Don't step to me or you're gonna get mushed
I'm doing 120 plowing over mail boxes
Radar detector to tell me where the cops is
Spend another night at the Motel 6
It's five dollars extra get the porno flicks
Concoct a black and tan in my brandy snifter
I'm a kleptomaniac K-Mart shoplifter
Cash flow getting low so I had to pull a job
I found a nice place to visit but a better place to rob
I left my car outside and the engine still revvin'
Time to get busy at 7-Eleven
Then I went inside to make my withdrawal
I saw what he had had but I had to take it all

Knucklehead deli tried to gyp me on the price
So I clocked him off the turban with the bag of ice
Cause I'm mellow like Jell-O cool like lemonade
I made my getaway and I thought that I had it made
I feel like Steve McQueen a former movie star
Look in my rearview mirror seen a police car
Ballantine quarts with the puzzle on the cap
I couldn't help but notice I was caught in a speed trap
Dirty mary crazy larry on the run from dirty harry
Stash the cash in the dash but my gun I did carry
I'm seeing blue and red flashing deep in the night
I got my alibi straight and I pulled over to the right
Cop knocked on my window and said Boy where's the fire
you've got a mailbox on your bumper and a bald front tire
Outta the car longhair your goose is cooked
Read me my rights fingerprinted and booked
Makin' like a D.T. driving a Gran Fury
Wherever I hang my hat's my home and my past is kind of blurry
Every dog will have its day and mine will be in front of a jury
I'm the high plains drifter and I'm never in a hurry
Read me my rights as if I didn't know this
Threw me in the tank with the drunk called Otis
With his five o' clock shadow he smelled of 3-day old beer
My man turned to me and said why are you here?
I said I'm charming and dashing i'm rental car bashing
Phony paper passing at Nix Check Cashing
I went before the judge he sent me to the Brooklyn House of D.
He said you behave son or we'll throw away the key
Harry Houdini'd out the cuffs I kicked the screw in the knee
Took the bailiff's wallet and went straight to O.T.B.
I had a good feeling easy come easy go
I bet on one horse to win and another to show
And sure enough that knak came in
Brought my ticket to the window and collected my win
Broke into my new car with a wire coat hanger
Hot wired hot wheeled and Suzy is a headbanger</song>
      <song title="Sounds of Science" track="5">Now here we go dropping science dropping it all over
Like bumping around the town like when you're driving a Range Rover
Expanding the horizons and expanding the parameters
Expanding the rhymes of sucker M.C. amateurs
Naugels, isaac newton scientific E.Z.
Ben Franklin with the kite getting over with the key
Rock shocking the mic as many times times the times tables
Rock well to tell dispel all of the old fables
I've been dropping the new science and kicking the new knowledge
An M.C. to a degree that you can't get in college
The dregs of the earth and the eggs that I eat
I've got pegs through my hands and one through my feet
Shea Stadium the Radium E M D squared
Got kicked out of the Palladium you think that I cared
It's the sound of science

Time and money for girls covered with honey
You lie and aspire to be as cunning
Reeling and rockin' and rollin' B size D cup
Order the quarter deluxe why don't you wake up
My mind is kinda flowin like an oil projector
Had to get up to get the Jimmy protector
Went berserk and worked and exploded
She woke up in the morning and her face was coated
Buddy you study the man on the mic
D. do what you like
Drunk a skunk am I from the celebration
To peep that freak unique penetration
I figured out who makes the crack
It's the suckers with the badges and the blue jackets
A professor of science cause I keep droppin' it
I smell weak cause you keep poppin' it
People always asking what's the phenomenon
Yo what's up know what's going on
No one really knows what I'm talking about
Yeah that's right my name's Yauch

Ponce de leon constantly on
The fountain of youth not Robotron
Peace is a word I've heard before
So move and move and move upon the dance floor
I'm gonna die gonna die one day
Cause I'm goin and goin and goin this way
Not like a roach or a piece of toast
I'm going out first class not going out coach
Rock my adidas never rock fila
I do not sniff the coke I only smoke sinsemilla
With my nose I knows and with my scopes I scope
What I live I write and that is strictly rope
I've got science for any occasion
Postulating theorems formulating equations
Cheech wizard in a snow blizzard
Eating chicken gizzards with a girl named Lizzy
Dropping science like when Galileo dropped the orange</song>
      <song title="3-Minute Rule" track="6">Stay up all night go to sleep watching Dragnet
Never sleep alone because Jimmy's the magnet
I'm so rope they call me Mr. Roper
When the troubles arise I'm the cool coper
On the mic I score just like the Yankees
Get over on Ms. Crabtree like my main man Spankee
Excuse me young lady I don't mean to trouble ya
But you're looking mighty fine inside your B.M.W.
I got lucky I brought home a kitten
Before I got busy I slipped on the mitten
Can't get better odds cause I'm a sure thing
Proud Mary keeps on turning rolling like a Ring Ding
Jump the turnstile never pay the toll
Doo wa diddy bust with the pre-roll
Customs jails me over an herb seed
Don't rat on your boy over some rat weed
I'm out of your back door and into another
Your boyfriend doesn't know about me and your mother
Not perfect grammar always perfect timing
The Mike stands for money and the D. is for diamonds

Roses are red the sky is blue
I got my barrel at your neck so what the fuck you gonna do
It's just two wheels and me the wind in my eyes
The engine is the music and my nine's by my side
Cause you know Y. A. U. C. H.
I'm takin' all M.C.'s out in the place
Takin' life as it comes no fool am I
I'm goin' off gettin' paid and I don't ask why
Playin' beats on my box makin' music for the many
Know alota def girls that would do anything
A lot of parents like to think I'm a villain
I'm just chillin' like Bob Dylan
I smoke cheeba it helps me with my brain
I might be a little dusted but I'm not insane
People come up to me and they try to talk shit man
I've been making records since you were sucking on your mother's dick

Girl you're walking tall now with your fancy clothes
You got fancy things going up your nose
You get fancy gifts from expensive men
You're a dog on a leash like a pig in a pen
Mothership connection getting girl's affection
If your life needs correction don't follow my direction
You got your 8 by 10 your agent your Harley
You be driving around Hollywood yes sorry charlie
Cause I'm running things like some Mack motherfucker
Your only claim to fame is you're a false fake sucker
You slip you slack you clock me you lack
While I'm reading on the road by my man Jack Kerouac
Poetry in motion coconut lotion
I had to diss the girl because she got too emotional
Are you experienced little girl
I want to know what goes on in your little girl world
Cause I'm on your mind it's hard to forget me
I'll take your pride for a ride if you let me
So peace out ya'll I'm PCP so I'm out
Full throttle to the bottle and full full clout
And I'm out</song>
      <song title="Hey Ladies" track="7">Hey ladies in the place I'm callin' out to ya
There never was a city kid truer and bluer
There's more to me than you'll ever know
And I've got more hits than Sadaharu Oh
Ton thumb tom cushman or tom foolery
Date women on T.V. with the help of Chuck Woolery
Words are flowing out just like the Grand Canyon
And I'm always out looking for a female companion
I threw the lasso around the tallest one and dragged her to the crib
I took off her moccasins and put on my bib
I'm wheelin' and dealin' I make a little bit of stealing
I'll bring you back to the place and your dress I'm peeling
Your body's on time and your mind is appealing
Staring at the cracks up there upon the ceiling
Some such nonsense is the bass that I'm throwing
Talking to a girl telling her I'm all knowing
She's talking to the kid to the who
I'm telling here every lie that you know that I never did
Hey ladies, get funky

Me in the corner with a good looking daughter
I dropped my drawers and it was welcome back Kotter
We were cutting up the rug she started cutting up the carpet
In my apartment I begged her please stop it
The gift of gab is the gift that I have
And that girl ain't nothing but a crab
Educated no stupid yes
And when I say stupid i mean stupid fresh
I'm not james at 15 or chachi in charge
I'm Adam and I'm adamant about living large
With the white sassoons and the looks that kill
Makin' love in the back of my Coupe De Ville
I met a little cutie she was all hopped up on zootie
I liked the little cutie but I kicked her in the bootie
Cause I don't kinda go for that messin' around
You be listening to my records' a number one sound
Step to the rhythm step step to the ride
I've got an open mind so why don't you all get inside
Tune in turn on to my tune that's live
Ladies flock like fish to my line
Hey ladies, get funky

She's got a gold tooth you know she's hardcore
She'll show you a good time then she'll show you the door
Break up with your girl it ended in tears
Vincent van gogh and mail that ear
I call her in the middle of the night when I'm drinking
The phone booth on the corner is damp and it's stinking
She said come on over it was me that she missed
I threw that trash can through her window cause you know I got dissed
Your old lady left you and you went girls&lt;i&gt;[x3]&lt;/i&gt; insane
You blew yourself up in the back of the 6 train
Take my advice at any price a gorilla like your mother is mighty weak
Sucking down pints till I didn't know
Woke up in the morning at the Won Ton Ho
Cause I announce I like girls that bounce
With the weight that pays about a pound per ounce
Girls with curls and big long locks
And beatnik chicks just wearing their smocks
Walking high and mighty like she's #1 and
She thinks she's the passionate one</song>
      <song title="Looking Down The Barrel of a Gun" track="8">I'm rolling down the hill snowballing getting bigger
An explosion in the chamber the hammer from the trigger
I seen him get stabbed I watched the blood spill out
He had more cuts than my man Chuck Chillout
24 is my age 22 is my gauge
I'm writing rhymes on a page going off in a rage
Out on a mission a stolen car mission
Had a little problem with the transmission
3 on the tree in the middle of the night
I have this steak on my head cause I got into a fist fight
Life comes in phases take the good with the bad
You bought those coins on the street and you got had
Because it's all high spirit you know you gotta hear it
Don't touch the mic baby don't come near it
It's gonna get you it's gonna get you
It's gonna get you girl it's gonna get you

Looking down the barrel of a gun
Son of a gun son of a bitch
Getting paid getting rich

Ultra violence running through my head
Fuzzy navel y'all making me see red
Rapid fire louie like rambo got bullets
I'm a gonna die harder like my kid Bruce Willis
I love girlies waxing and milking
Coordinating chics is my man Dave Scilkin
Predetermined destiny is who I am
You got your finger on the trigger like the Son of Sam
I am like Clockwork Orange going off on the town
I've got homeboys bonanza to beat your ass down
I'm mad at my desk and I'm writing all curse words
Expressing my aggressions through my schizophrenic verse words
You're a headless chicken chasin' a sucker free basin
Looking for a fist to put your face in
Get hip don't slip knuckle heads
Racism is schism on the serious tip</song>
      <song title="Car Thief" track="9">Some static started in the pool hall
Hit a motherfucker's face with the cue ball
Then I met this girl she tried to gank me
So I smacked her in the booty with M.C. Plank Bee
Me and my crew out breaking windows
The bingo the lotto you know I'll never win those
Possession is half the law
I had my routines before all y'all
Your whole life is coming apart at the seams
You ain't nothing but a car thief biting routines
I'm a city slicker I ain't no townie
Right now I wish i had another hash brownie
Like Ricky always said you've got to toke and pass
Or Mookie's gonna kick your fuckin' ass
You try to take what isn't yours like a God damn rat
See personally I wouldn't want to go out like that

I'm a writer a poet a genius I know it
I don't buy cheeba I grow it Marijuana
People always trying to get next to me
I had a beautiful experience on Ecstasy
Smoked up a bag of elephant tranquilizer
Because I had to deal with a money hungry miser
Had a caine filled Kool with my man Rush Rush
Saw my teeth fall in the sink when I started to brush
You be doing nose candy on the Bowie Coke Mirror
My girl asked for some but I pretended not to hear her
You can't deny me you always want to try me
You're just gonna get your ass kicked
Homeboy throw in the towel
Your girl got dicked by Ricky Powell
The Godfather of Soul is in the belly of the beast
For smoking that dust at St. Anthony's Feast

All the wife beaters and all the tax cheaters
Sitting in the White House pulling their peters
Buy my cheeba from the cop down the street
The only cop with a rope chain walking the beat
Like a sneaky pouch time bomb tickin'
Like the beat to my rhyme just kickin'
Space cake cookies I discover who I am
I'm a dusted old bummy Hurdy Gurdy Man
Five-O caught me now I'm going to the mountains
Said good-bye to my girl my lawyers and accountants
My mind is kinda rhymin and I think I oughta think
So I'm rockin all the rhymes and I'll have another drink
So the lights are flashing my mind is spinning
I feel like it is always the beginning
Of another rhyme I'm rapping M.C.'ing I rock
You ain't nothing but a car thief who must be stopped</song>
      <song title="What Comes Around" track="10">Soft overripe fresh skeezed California females
With 3-inch cherry red press-on Lee nails
Reach into my mind for the rhymes I'm seeking
Like a garbage bag full overflowing now it's leaking
Rapunzel Rapunzel let down your hair
So I can climb up and get into your underwear
Rat soup eating test cheating no business punk
You're insecure born in the junkyard with the junk
You've gone wet look crazy and messed with your head
You fucked around and wound up with the bald skin head
You're all mixed up like pasta primavera
Why'd you throw that chair at Geraldo Rivera man
Cause one man's ceiling is another man's floor
So get that money out of your ass you whore
I brought her upstairs onto the roof
I dogged your wife and she is a doofus
What goes around, comes around

Clean B cleaning the G spot you know that we've got
Dolemite's house and you have not
Look out my window look over the city
With two black eyes your girl ain't that pretty
Why you wanna beat that brat with a bat
Why you wanna treat your girl like that
Living in the rat race smoking rat weed
You reap what you sow when you plant the seed
Bum cheese on rye with ham and prosciutto
Got more louie than phil rizzuto
What goes around, comes around

Funky pam, F.P.</song>
      <song title="Shadrach" track="11">Riddle me this brother can you handle it
Your style to my style you can't hold a candle to it
Equinox symmetry and the balance is right
Smokin' and drinkin' on a Tuesday night
It's not how you play the game it's how you win it
I cheat and steal and sin and I'm a cynic
For those about to rock we salute you
The dirty thoughts for dirty minds we contribute to
I once was lost but now I'm found
The music washes over and you're one with the sound
Who shall inherit the earth the meek shall
I think I'm starting to peak now al
And then the man upstairs well I hope that he cares
If I had a penny for my thoughts I'd be a millionaire
We're just 3 M.C.'s and we're on the go
Shadrach mesach abednago

Only 24 hours in a day
Only 12 notes a man can play
Music for all and not just one people
And now we're gonna bust with the Putney Swope sequel
More Adidas sneakers that a plumber got pliers
Got more suites that Jacoby &amp; Meyers
If not for my vices my bugged out desires
My year would be good just like Goodyear's tires
So I'm out pickin' pockets at the Atlantic Antic
And nobody wants to hear you cause your rhymes are so frantic
I mix business with pleasure way too much
I mean wine and women and song and such
I don't get blue I gotta mean red streak
You don't pay the band your friends and that's weak
Get even like Steven like pulling a Rambo
Shadrach mesach abednago

Steal from the rich and I'm out robbing banks
Give to the poor and I always give thanks
Got more stories that J.D. got Salinger
I hold the title and you are the challenger
I've got money like Charles Dickens
Got the girlies in the Coupe like the Colonel's got the chickens
Always go out dapper like Harry S. Truman
I'm madder than Mad's Alfred E. Newman
Never gonna let them say that I don't love you

My noggin is hoggin all kinds of thoughts
Adam Yoggin is Yauch and he's rockin of course
Smoke the holy chalice got my own religion
Rally round the stage and check the funky dope musicians
Jerry lee swaggert or jerry lee falwell
You love mario andretti cause he always drives his car well
Vicious circle of reality since the day you were born
And we love the hot butter on what the popcorn
Sippin on wine and mackin
Rockin on the stage with all the hands clappin
Ride the wave of fate it don't ride me
Being very proud to be an M.C.
And the man upstairs I hope that he cares
If I had a penny for my thoughts I'd be a millionaire
Amps and crossovers under my rear hood
The bass is bumpin from the back of my Fleetwood
They tell us what to do hell no
Shadrach mesach abednago</song>
      <song title="B-Boy Bouillabaisse" track="12">&lt;i&gt;[Get On the Mic]&lt;/i&gt;

Get on the mic Mike let's be real and don't cloud the issue
The rhymes are dope an M.C. you must listen to
People say that they been missin' me and missin' you
Get on the mic and let's show them like we used to
You say fuck that yo holmes fuck this
The king ad-whammy your dick butkus
One half science and the other half soul
His name's mike D. not fat morton jelly roll
M.C. busy le disco fooled around in fresno
Got over on your girlie cause you know she never says no
Well mike D. is a special individual
Pulling out knots pulling in residuals
Go to the movies get the Rolos the cholos riding slow and low
Mike on the mic and bust with the solo
Mike my stromy don't be so selfish
Get on the mic cause you know you eat shellfish


&lt;I&gt;[stop that train]&lt;/i&gt;

It's 4:00 a.m. I've got the Dr. Hfuhruhurr Ale
I've got nothing to lose so I'm pissin' on the third rail
Groggy eyed and fried I'm headed for the station
D-Train ride to Coney Island vacation
Dedicated to the boofers in the back of the 1 train
They'll be kicking out windows high on cocaine
Then I ump the turnstyle I lost my last token
Riding between the cars pissing smoking
Head for the last car fluorescent light blackout
Policeman told my homeboy put that crack out
You know you light up when the lights go down
Then you read the New York Post Fulton St. downtown
Same faces every day but you don't know their names
Party people going placed on the D-Train

Trench coat wing tip going to work
And you'll be pulling a train like Captain Kirk
Pick pocket gangsters paying their debts
I caught a bullet in the lung from Bernie Goetz
Overworked and underpaid staring at the floor
Prostitutes spandex caught in the slide doors
Stuck between the stations it seems like an eternity
Sweating like sardines in a flophouse fraternity
$50.00 fine for disturbing the peace
The neck tortoise your Lees are creased
Hot cup of coffee and the donuts are Dunkin
Friday night and Jamaica Queens funkin
Elevated platform never gonna conform
Riding over the diner where I always get my toast warm
Bust into the conductor's booth and busted out rhymes
Over the loud speaker about the hard times
Sat across from a man readin El Diario
Riding the train down from El Barrio
Went from the station straight to Orange Julius
I bought a hot dog from my man George Drakoulias


&lt;i&gt;[Year and a Day]&lt;/i&gt;

M.C. for what I AM and do
the A is for Adam and the lyrics; true
so as pray and hope and the message is sent
And I am living in the dreams that i have dreamt
because I'm down with the three the unstoppable three
Me and adam and D. were born to M.C.
and my body and soul and mind are pure
not polluted or diluted or damaged beyond cure
just lyrics from I to you recited
arrested, bailed but cuffed and indicted
enter the arena as I take center stage
the lights set low and the night has come of age
take the microphone in hand as that I am a professional
speak my knowledge to the crowd and the ed. is special
For I am a bard but not the last one
I'm my own king and this is my castle
dwell in realms of now but vidi those of the past
seen a glimpse from ahead and I don't think it's gonna last
and you can bet your ass

I drop the L. when I'm skiing 
I'm smoking and peaking
I put the skis on the roof almost every single weekend
can't stop the mindfuck when it's rolling along
can't stop the smooth runnin's when the shit's running strong
broke my bindings the lion with wings
preaching his word in the B. Boy sing
I AM one with myself as I turn to The
I prefer the dreams to reality
I prefer my life don't need no other man's wife
don't need no crazy lifestyle with stress and strife
but it's good to have turn to be a king for a day
or for a week or for a year or for a year in a day
come what may

I'm fishing with my boat and I'm fishing for trout
Mix the bass ale with the guiness stout
fishing for a line inside my brain
and looking out at the world through my window pane
every day has many colors cuz the glass is stained
everything has changed but remains the same
so once again the mirror raised and I see myself as clear as day
And I am going to the limits of my ultimate destiny
feeling as though Somebody were testing me
He who sees the end from the beginning of time
looking forward through all the ages is, was and always shall be
check the prophetic sections of the pages

He goes by the name of Disco Dave


&lt;i&gt;[Hello Brooklyn]&lt;/i&gt;

Hello Brooklyn

New york new york it's a hell of a town
The Bronx is up and I'm Brooklyn down
They don't know my name they only know my initials
Building bombs in the attic for elected officials
I quit my job I cut my hair
I cut my boss cause I don't care
You tried to get slick you bust a little chuckle
You're gonna get smacked with my gold finger knuckle
Cause being as fly as me is something you never thought of
You'll be sticking up old ladies with the hand gun or the sawed-off
Like a buffalo soldier I'm broader than Broadway
Keep keepin' on I don't care what they say
I play my stereo loud it disturbs my neighbors
I want to enjoy the fruits of my labor
Cause I am the holder of the 3-pack Bonanza
If you open the book then you will get your hand slapped
I am the keeper of the 3-pack Bonanza
If you ask a question you will get the answer
Her breast I saw i reached i felt
M.O.N.E.Y. the belt
I stay at home just like a hermit
I got the jammy but I don't got the permit
Yes you got a boyfriend and indeed his name is Slick Nick
that is why Annabelle you're caught with the shrimpy limp dick trick
I ride around town cause my ride is fly
I shot a man in Brooklyn just to watch him die


&lt;i&gt;[Dropping Names]&lt;/i&gt;

He thrusts his fists against the post and still insists he sees a ghost
He thrusts his fists against the post and still insists he sees a ghost
She's slippin through his fingers as she's movin' out to the coast
He thrusts his fists against the post and still insists he sees a ghost

If your world was all black and if your world was all white
Then you wouldn't get much color out of life now right
Nicknamed Shamrock my name is not Shamus
Girlies on the tippy cause my homie is famous
My name is not O'Houigheighi Nor is it Brian
If I said that I was weak you know I'd be lyin'
Suckers try to bite they try to pursue it
If you explain to a musician he'll tell that he knows it but he just can't do it


&lt;I&gt;[lay it on me]&lt;/i&gt;

Chinese eyes and Chinese suits
Smokin' much buddha and smokin' much boots
More updated on the hip-hop lingo
My favorite new york knick was hawthorne wingo
Met a girl at a party and I gave her my card
You know that it said Napoleon Bonaparte
Peepin' out the colors I be buggin' on Cezanne
They call me Mike D Joe Blow the Lover Man
Your face turns red as your glass of wine
You spilled on my lyrics as you wasted my time
Girl you should be with me you should drop that bum
Cause I got more flavor than Fruit Striped Gum
With that big round butt of yours
I'd like to butter your muffin I'm not bluffin'
Serve you on a platter like Thanksgiving stuffin'


&lt;i&gt;[Mike On the Mic]&lt;/i&gt;

Here's another one for y'all to peep
It's called m-I-k-e on the m-i-C. 

I met this girl last night with a peculiar cackle
I laid the bait and then she took the tackle
Had too much to drink at the Red Lobster
Now the room is spinning around like the blades of a helicopter
I never met a girl that was too finicky
If the press has their way then they're going to finish me
You might know this but you've never been this see
If I ate spinach then I'd be called Spinach D
I shed light like cats shed fur
Ride around town like Raymond Burr
I'm so high that they call me Your Highness
If you don't know me then pardon my shyness
I live in the Village wherever I go I walk to
I keep my friends around so I have someone to talk to
I play my music loud because you know it's got clout to it
It's a trip it's got a funky beat and I can bug out to it</song>
    </album>
    <album name="To The 5 Boroughs" year="2004">
      <song title="Ch-Check It Out" track="1">All you trekkies and tv addicts 
Don't mean to diss 
Don't mean to bring static 
All you klingons in the fucking house 
Grab your backstreet friend and get loud 
Blowin' doors off hinges 
I'll grab you with the pinchers 
And no i didn't retire 
I'll snatch you up 
With the needle nose pliers 

Like mutual of omaha 
Got the ill boat 
You've never seen before 
Gliding in the glades 
And like lorne greene 
You know i get paid 
Like caprese and with the basil 
Not goofy like darren or hazel 
I'm a mother fucking nick at night with 
Classics rerunning that you know all right 
Now remain calm no alarm 
Cause my farm ain't fat 
So what's up with that 
I've got friends and family that i respect 
When i think i'm too good 
They put me in check 
So believe when i say i'm no better than you 
Except when i rap 
So i guess it ain't true 
Like that y'all and you just don't stop 
Guaranteed to make your body rock 

Check-ch-check-check-check-ch-check it out 
What-wha-what-what-what's it all about 
Work-wa-work-work-work-wa-work it out 
Let's turn this motherfuckin' party out 

Said, &quot;doc what's the condition 
I'm a man that's on a mission&quot; 
Said, &quot;son, you'd better listen 
Stuck in your ass 
Is an electrician&quot; 
Like a scientist 
Mmmm when i'm applying this 
Method of controlling my mind 
Like einstein and the rappin' duke combined 
Hey baby bubba now what the deal 
I didn't know you go for that mass appeal 
Some call it salugi 
Some hot potato 
I stole your mic and you won't see it later 
Cause i work magic like a magician 
I add up like a mathematician 
I'm a bank cashier 
Engineer 
I wear cotton but i don't wear sheer 

Shazam and abracadabra 
In the whip i'm gonna cruise past ya 
Yo money, don't chump yourself 
Put that shit back on the shelf 
Light rays blazin' 
You're out of phase 
And my crews amazin' 
We're working on the record yo 
So stay patient 

Check-ch-check-check-check-ch-check it out
What-wha-what-what-what's it all about
Work-wa-work-work-work-wa-work it out
Let's turn this motherfuckin' party out 

Now, i go by the name of the king adrock 
I don't wear a cup nor a jock 
I bring the shit that's beyond bizarre 
Like miss piggy 
Who moi 
I am the one with the clientele. 
You say, &quot;adrock, you rock so well&quot; 
I've got class like pink champale 
Mca grab the mic before the mic goes stale 

Don't test me 
They can't arrest me 
I'll fake right cross-over and shoot lefty 
You look upset, yo calm down 
You look cable guy dunked off of your crown 
I flow like smoke out a chimney 
You never been me 
You wanna rap but what you're making ain't hip hop b 

Get your clothes right out the dryer 
Put armor all up on your tire 
Sport that fresh attire 
Tonight we goin' out set the town on fire 
Set the town ablaze 
Gonna stun and amaze 
Ready to throw a craze 
Make your granny shake her head 
And say, &quot;those were the days&quot; 

Check-ch-check-check-check-ch-check it out 
What-wha-what-what-what's it all about 
Work-wa-work-work-work-wa-work it out 
Let's turn this motherfuckin' party out</song>
      <song title="Right Right Now Now" track="2">Once upon a time up on this mic 
MC's be really workin' on what they write 
With the sound delight we rock all night 
And yes we're gonna party for the right to fight 
We're international like Matt Takei 
Rock the mic from Munich out to Taipei 
Still around the way is where we'll stay 
Say what we mean, mean what we say 
Trajectories from the past are taking their toll and 
What we do now is future moulding 
Columbine bowling, childhood stolen 
We need a bit more gun controlling 

Right, right, now, now 
What is goin' on? 
We, we, gotta, gotta 
Get it goin' on 
Be, be, fore, fore 
It's too far gone 
We gotta work together, it's been too long 

When I get on you scream &quot;Hoo Tight!&quot; 
Rockin' this flow I could go all night 
I'm not here to fight, or incite 
I'm like the beach in the Bahamas make you feel alright 
I'm getting kind of tired of the situation 
The US attacking other nations 
And narration, on every station 
False election's got me losing my patience 
I'm a funky-ass Jew and I'm on my way 
And yes I got to say fuck the kkk 
And oh yeah hey, how about today? 
If you want to set it off then let me hear you say 

Right, right, now, now 
What is goin' on? 
We, we, gotta, gotta 
Get it goin' on 
Be, be, fore, fore 
It's too far gone 
We gotta work together, it's been too long 

I went to get a loan and they asked my race 
I wrote down human inside the space 
It's a disgrace how they try to debase 
It ain't the bank's damn business how my lineage trace 
Now let me drop a verse that's terse and concise 
I'm an iron chef when I slice and dice 
With the rhyme precise, the word is nice 
So please pass me the Reunite on ice 
Well let's go to work and not beserk 
'Cause when the time comes the body goes to dirt 
Try to smooth it out like Levert 
Keep the mind alert and not revert 

Right, right, now, now 
What is goin' on? 
We, we, gotta, gotta 
Get it goin' on 
Be, be, fore, fore 
It's too far gone 
We gotta work together, it's been too long</song>
      <song title="3 The Hard Way" track="3">Fresh dressed 'cause I shop at models 
Deep in brooklyn I ride the elevated trains 
Used to ride the D to beat the morning bell 
At edward R. morrow out on ave l 
We be grillin' cheese and flippin' flapjacks 
With the diamond stylus we cutting wax 
We're the super elastic bubble plastic 
Got ethereal material that's straight up classic 
You try to vex reject but you should respect 
Or we'll have JC send you out a FedEx * 1 
So don't start to flex up in the discotheque 
Or we'll make you extinct tyrannosaurus rex 

We're gonna rock this motherfucker like three the hard way 

Your rhyme technique, it is antique 
To all my heads Qu'est-ce-que tu fabriques? 
Que cosa fai? Come sta e? 
Ho fato molte telefonate 
Oops gotcha clutch like Plazza 
Sneak between the sheets so hide like matzoh 
Holler back challah bread... next 
We are the crew who put the crew in Cruex 
I can see that Def Jam doesn't recognize me 
I'm mike d the one who put the satin in your panties 
Time to count MC's in this place to be 
Not five, not four, not two, just three 

We're gonna rock this motherfucker like three the hard way 

Round-house kick the mic out your hand 
Drunken mantis, my name brand 
So if you're slick with the tricks and the slight of hand 
I'm hip top the shit that you're trying to scam 
Gnip gnop I got shit to pop 
I'm an exceptional professional that just don't stop 
So pack up your bag and your mic and don't wait 
E.T. phone home now get the fuck out my face 
You know we shake'em bake'em then we take'em 
Treat MCs like leaves go out and rake'em 
If you sell our CDs on Canal before we make'em 
Then we will have no alternative but to serve you 
on a platter like Steak'Em 

We're gonna rock this motherfucker like three the hard way</song>
      <song title="It Takes Time To Build" track="4">If you don't like the news then press eject 
Baby Davis getting older can't take a rain check 
It's time to let'em know what we expect 
Stop building suv's strung out on opec 
Hold up wait up you know we come correct 
You wanna change things up, well hey just get set 
It's easier to sit back than stick out your neck 
It's easier to break things than build it correct 
We've got a president we didn't elect 
The Kyoto treaty he decided to neglect 
And still the US just wants to flex 
Keep doin' that wop we gonna break our necks 

It takes a second to wreck it 
It takes time to build 
You gots to chill 

Hate filled people wanna keep us in check 
Tearin' down each other is what they expect 
If you want love well hey that's a bet 
We've got to give before we can get 
Waiting like a batter who is on deck 
When it's time to wreck shop then shop I'll wreck 
So let's calibrate and check our specs 
We need a little shift on over towards the left 
I don't really know but I suspect 
I think it's due time that we inspect 
How they get their information and their facts are checked 
Another press conference someone's talking out their neck 

It takes a second to wreck it 
It takes time to build 
You gots to chill 

So step up to the window and place your bets 
Is the us gonna keep breaking necks 
Maybe it's time that we impeach Tex 
And the military muscle that he wants to flex 
By the time Bush is done what will be left 
Selling votes like E-pills at the discotheque 
Environmental destruction and the national dept 
But plenty of dollars left in the fat war chest 
What the real deal why you can't connect 
Why you hating people that you never met 
Didn't your mama teach you to show some respect? 
Why not open your mind for a sec? 

It takes a second to wreck it 
It takes time to build 
You gots to chill</song>
      <song title="Rhyme The Rhyme Well" track="5">Now my name is Adrock I've got a story to tell 
When I rock the crowd the crowd we all yell 
And when I get the feeling i feel the feel swell 
And when I start to rhyme well i rhyme the rhyme well 

Oh you didn't know I got the flow 
I could sing, rap, dance in just one show 
With the cornbread stuffin' with the Blimpie Bluffin 
Mother fuckin' yosi with the goddamn muffins 
Hey could you please pass me the peas 
And let me get a tissue if you think your're gonna sneeze 
I'm the player and the coach I'm no roach 
I bought my grandma a brand new broach 

Well I'm mca with a story to tell 
When I rock the crowd I rock the crowd well 
And when I get the feeling i feel the feel swell 
'cause when I start to rhyme well i rhyme the rhyme well 

'Cause I'm a craftsman, who ain't fastin' 
I'll take you to task everyone of ya'll draftsman 
I'm rehearsin' and ain't maskin' 
Bringin' the beat back and keepin' it lastin' 
Keepin' it top notch, beyond passing 
Simmer in the pan 'cause, I ain't flashin' 
I'm party crashin' so you better batten 
Down those hatches stop procrastin- 

Well I'm mike d with a story to tell 
And when I rock the crowd the crowd we all yell 
And when I get the feeling i feel the feel swell 
'cause when I start to rhyme well i rhyme the rhyme well 

Went to the top and never went pop and 
Came back down but still not stopping 
I'm not even asking, &quot;Yo what's cracking?&quot; 
Serving MC's on a platter like baked Alaskan 
So start packing because I'm back in 
The game of hiphop reprenting Manhattan 

Now push the pause button then start ducking 
Shhhhh you heard me like I'm E.F. Hutton, 
Hutton shhhhhhhh, hutton shhh, hutton shhhhhhh, 
Hutton SHHHHHHHHH!!!!</song>
      <song title="Triple Trouble" track="6">If You 
If You 
Wanna Know 
Wanna Know 
The real deal about the three 
Well let me tell you 
We're triple trouble ya'll 
We're gonna bring you up to speed 

Cause I'm a specializer, rhyme reviser 
Ain't selling out to advertisers 
What you get is what you see 
And you won't see me out there advertising 
See I like to party not drink Bacardi
'Cause I'm not looking to throw up on nobody 
Known for my spiel like wheelie one wheel 
'Cause this is like having a delicious meal 

Moving the crowd, well that's a must 
I got some words that apply to us and that's 
Mesmerizing, tantalizing 
Captivating, we're devastating 

If You 
If You 
Wanna Know 
Wanna Know 
The real deal about the three 
Well let me tell you 
We're triple trouble ya'll 
We're gonna bring you up to speed 

Here's one for the bleachers and the upper tier 
Versatile like all-temp-a-cheer 
If you wanna drink call Mr. Belvedere 
Run this rap game like a brigadier 
I got kicks on the one, seven and eleven 
Snares on the five and thirteen 
Rhymes on time and that's the given 
We're hot on the disco scene check it a check it 
Slow down with I-me, got to stop stingin' 
The source of the problem is at the origin 
You've got lyrics that have got me cringin' 
You're like a fish-wife, quit your damn whingin' 

If You 
If You 
Wanna Know 
Wanna Know 
The real deal about the three 
Well let me tell you 
We're triple trouble ya'll 
We're gonna bring you up to speed 

Hey yo, bam super nature god damn 
Cerrone on the microphone I am 
Adrock a.k.a sharp cheddar 
My rhymes are better 
What the helen in troy is that? 
Did I hear you say my rhymes is wack? 
I'm beautiful you can't touch me 
If you pick a rose, well you might just bleed 

We're originators you can't feign 
Ignorance or pass the blame 
'Nuff rhymes coming out the brain 
'Nuff beats to drive you insane 
'Nuff moves to make your neck crane 
'Nuff skill to make the rhymes ingrain 
'Nuff heat to leave you in flames 
'Nuff style that you can't defame 
You see I walk like jabba the hutt 
With the style so new y'all be like what? 
Turn the party out like a bon vivant 
With the skill at will that I know you want 
On a hot day sip on iced latte 
Devious like wyllie coyote 
Hot to trote or maybe not-e 
'Cause little did they know there was a baby in her body 

Mesmerizing, tantalizing, captivating, devastating 

If You 
If You 
Wanna Know 
Wanna Know 
The real deal about the three 
Well let me tell you 
We're triple trouble ya'll 
We're gonna bring you up to speed 

Roses are beautiful to look at, but they're thorny 
Stems may cause them to be difficult to handle 
thus making their beauty a bit awkward</song>
      <song title="Hey Fuck You" track="7">Which of you schnooks took my rhyme book? 
Look give it back you're wicky wack 
With your ticky tack calls didn't touch you at all 
I didn't touch your hand man you know its all ball 
You sold a few records but don't get slick 
'Cause you used a corked bat to get those hits 
You've been in the game, your career is long 
But when you break it down you've only got 2 songs 
MC's are like clay pigeons and I'm shootn' skeet 
I just yell pull and MMM drops the beat 
You people call yourselves MC's but you're garbage men 
Takin' out the trash when you pull out the pen 

And if you don't like then hey fuck you! 

I read about you up on page 6 
They was trashin' your ass it's sad you're getting dissed 
Now talk about your face now don't get pissed 
But I suggest you see a dermatologist 
I keep that hot sauce hot not mild and weak 
It's gonna burn your mouth until you wet your beak 
I've got billions and billions of rhymes to flex 
'Cause I've got more rhymes than Carl Sagan's got turtlenecks 
Your rhymes are fake like a Canal Street watch 
You're hearing me and you're like &quot;oh my god its Sasquatch!&quot; 
I'm walkin' on water while you're stepping in shit 
So put your sewer boots on before your ass gets lit 

And if you don't like then hey fuck you! 
So put a quarter in your ass cause you played yourself 

Sucker MC's it's me they're resenting 
In the animal kingdom they call it presenting 
With the dipsy doodle the kit and caboodle 
The truth is brutal your grandma's kugel 
Kings County is my stomping ground 
The albee square mall, brooklyn, downtown 
So don't ask me to wine and dine ya 
I'm from brooklyn you're from regina 
You're like foghorn leghorn, yosemite sam 
You're just yellin' and wildin' wondering who I am 
With those lies you're telling you look like Toucan Sam 
But my style's impregnable like the Hoover Dam 

And if you don't like then hey fuck you!</song>
      <song title="Oh Word?" track="8">Yo what the schnitzel we're back 
Shit's getting duller and duller and that's a fact 
I don't care what you heard or care what you seen 
I swear it wasn't me in Bear magazine 
Because I'm not that hairy oh contrary 
I go with the flow though the tempo varies 
So twist the cap and pop the cork 
My name's adrock made in new york 

Oh word? 

What the ponytail, I don't eat snail 
I'll steal your keys and then I'll check your mail 
'Cause I'm the creepy crawler that be crawling your walls 
And I'm the shot caller when it comes to shot calls 
And I'll be rockin' parties from block to block 
And block party to party the neighborhoods on lock 
So hide your eyes, wait, I saw you looking 
The name's mcs made in downtown brooklyn 

Oh word? 

Yo what the parsley, parsley to the teeth 
I'm a rhyme style writer you're a rhyme style thief 
I may be paranoid you tried to fade me 
Here's a song for you &quot;Lady&quot; 
Make you bug out like you don't know what to do 
Your momma says &quot;shame on you&quot; 
When you're dancing with your crew 
So get that poor chicken up off your fork 
My name's mike d made in new york 

Oh word? 

Yo what the talafel you gotta get up awful 
Early to fool Mr. Furley 
And that's word to Aunt Shirley and you could 
Stick your head in the toilet give yourself a swirley 
Listen up biters go please stop 
While I'm politicin' at Murray's Cheese Shop 
Believe what you heard when you talk 
My name is Adrock made in New York 

Oh word? 
What the phone booth word to hair moose 
You're on the corner and you're selling a hog's tooth 
Don't mean to dis but I've got to point out 
The hogs tooth belong inside the hog's mouth 
Like ernest shackleton said to ord lees 
I'll have dog pemmican with my tea 
Now pass the wok 'cause I'm cookin' 
The names mcs made in downtown brooklyn 

Oh word? 

Yo, what the doofus, say good night 
You're snidely whiplash I'm dudley do-you-right 
Times are off the hinges leave your 2 way at the door 
We're all up the creek a long way from shore 
Not walking around looking to get you cake 
The D is for Diamonds not for Drakes 
This not a fantasy and I'm not Mr. O'Rourke 
The name's mike d made in new york 

Oh word?</song>
      <song title="That's It That's All" track="9">Back on the scene for ya'll people's delight 
You want peace for the people then ya say alright 
'cause george w's got nothing on me 
We got to take the power from he 
When I'm on the mic I feel good to go 
Like a snow day for school with hot cocoa 
So don't speak what I heard, just say what I know 
And my zodiac sign is Scorpio 
Look what the cat dragged in 
The creme de la creme without the skin 
So take a rest and mind your own biz 

And that's it that's all that's all there is 

Fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 
That's fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 

One for brooklyn, two for manhattan 
Let's go to work, get those hands clappin' 
Make you bounce, rock, roll and skate 
Don't underrate how I operate 
It ain't what you say, it's what you mean 
Intention leads to action, that is my theme 
So pay attention now as I begin to recap 
Puttin' words and ideas stacked back to back 

Some rhymes go flat, well mine go fizz 
I got no time for the drama 'cause stress is for kids 
'Cause when you're dead and buried well you got no biz 

And that's it that's all that's all there is 

Fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 
That's fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 

Brand new 

The time and place for the mind is here and now 
Keep the mind present less to worry about 
But like the hammer to the nail hit the nail on the head 
Well I don't shoot blanks and I don't shoot lead 
Well I'm a freaky streaker like Winnie the Pooh 
T-shirt and no pants and I dance the bugaloo 
Like george whipple on new york one 
Got a hairy ass and that's no fun 
I'm in the rhyme zone a different time zone 
And on the microphone you know that I'm at home 
It's time we looked past all our differences 
An' that's it that's all that's all there is 
Come on 

Fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 
That's fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 

An' that's 
Fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you 
That's fresh...fresh...fresh...for you...for you...for you</song>
      <song title="All Lifestyles" track="10">Ideas spark my hand grabs a pen 
Sweeten up the sound let me get the right blend 
Coming down the wire to the Neve mic pre 
Nice up the sound for the A to D 
I'm a wonderama snake can winner 
Bagel from bob and a tv dinner 
I'm the one that one that dance contest 
'Cause you know I dance the best 
All you gotta do is do your thing you see 
'Cause I don't give a fuck who you're supposed to be 
My name is Adrock and I aim to please 
And I gotta spread love in society 

We gotta keep the party going on 
All lifestyles, sizes, shapes, and form 

What you saw what you heard 
I get involved I might disturb 
And if you want what's going down 
You might just get that silky sound 
So what'cha want? So what'cha need? 
I've got the fonts you want to read 
Get in the game you gotta scheme 
All the same I've got the team 
More new wave not OG 
Walking down the block you say &quot;Yo D! 
When you coming out with the new CD 
That spreads love in society?&quot; 

We gotta keep the party going on 
All lifestyles, sizes, shapes, and form 

Goto goto goto goto 
Don't mess with crack or the baking soda 
Whether in the high rise where you live like Roda 
Or in the shack and you live like Yoda 
Once again it's on like a brand new morn 
Beatsie beatsie boys here to keep you all warm 
All you spazzes and you freaks 
Go and do your thing 'cause you're unique 
If it don't hurt nobody else than 
Don't be afraid to be yourself and 
Special dedication and so on 
to all lifestyles, sizes, shapes and forms 
We gotta keep the party going on 
All lifestyles, sizes, shapes, and form</song>
      <song title="Shazam!" track="11">Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Huh huh huh huh, Shazam! 

I sneak a chicken tikka 
Marsala at a gala event 
I represent that's stupid that's for sure 
You be like &quot;oh yeah Adam, real mature&quot; 
I'd like a lettuce, tomato and Munster on rye 
All this cheese is gonna make me cry 
Gorgonzola, Provolone 
Don't even get me started on this microphone 
Blowin' up like my name is Joe Bazooka 
I'm a super-dooper MC party pooper 
On a track so slick it'll make you feel all queasy 
Make you do like Fred Sanford with &quot;I'm comin' Wheezy!&quot; 
 
Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Huh huh huh huh, Shazam! 

On the court I go by the name Praying Mantis 
Got the edge and I've got the advantage 
If you could see things from my vantage 
Point then you could better understand this 
I'm in the lab all day I scrabble all night 
I got a bedazzler so my outfit's tight 
When it comes to panache I can't be beat 
I got the most style from below 14th street 
Internationally known as the Keebler Elf 
Can't keep a catalog up on the shelf 
I splash on beats like sauce on spaghetti 
Putting MC's out of business like they're Crazy Eddie 

Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Huh huh huh huh, Shazam! 

I know you're sitting pretty in the Hampty Hamps 
Posing like you're rolling with that camp 
In layman's terms let me break it down 
You're flipping and flopping just like a flounder 
I'm a hip hop scholar while you're left back 
So Jeckle and Rush go back to Lefrac 
I'm a simple man like Chance Gardner 
Working 9 to 5 Dolly Parton 
Got rhymes for jerks that's bringing on drama 
Which rhyme you want first? The one about your mama? 
Goodness gracious golly gee 
Shazam! Freeeeeeak out with the genie! 

Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Everybody get down huh 
Huh huh huh huh, Shazam! 

Freak out with the genie....</song>
      <song title="An Open Letter To NYC" track="12">Brooklyn, bronx, queens and staten 
From the battery to the top of manhattan 
Asian, Middle-Eastern and Latin 
Black, white, new york you make it happen 

Brownstones, water towers, trees, skyscrapers 
Writers, prize fighters and Wall Street traders 
We come together on the subway cars 
Diversity unified, whoever you are 
We're doing fine on the One and Nine line 
On the l we're doin' swell 
On the number Ten bus we fight and fuss 
'Cause we're thorough in the boroughs and that's a must 
I remember when the Duece was all porno flicks 
Running home after school to play PIX * 1 
At lunch I'd go to blimpies down on montague street 
And hit the Fulton Street Mall for the sneakers on my feet 
Dear new york I hope you're doing well 
I know a lot's happen and you've been through hell 
So, we give thanks for providing a home 
Through your gates at Ellis Island we passed in droves 

Brooklyn, bronx, queens and staten 
From the battery to the top of manhattan 
Asian, Middle-Eastern and Latin 
Black, white, new york you make it happen 

The L.I.E. the B.Q.E 
Hippies at the band shell with the L.S.D. 
Get my bvd's from vim 
You know I'm reppin' manhattan the best i can 
Stopped off at Bleeker Bob's got thrown out 
Sneakin' in at 4:00 am after going out 
You didn't rob me in the park at Dianna Ross 
But everybody started looting when the light went off 
From the south south bronx on out to queens bridge 
From hollis queens right down to bay ridge 
From castle hill to the lower east side 
From 1010 wins to live at five 
Dear new york this is a love letter 
To you and how you brought us together 
We can't say enough about all you do 
'Cause in the city were ourselves and electric too 

Brooklyn, bronx, queens and staten 
From the battery to the top of manhattan 
Asian, Middle-Eastern and Latin 
Black, white, new york you make it happen 

Shout out the South Bronx where my mom hails from 
Right next to High Bridge across from Harlem 
To the grand concourse where my mom and dad met 
Before they moved on down to the Upper West 
I see you're still strong after all that's gone on 
Life long we dedicate this song 
Just a little something to show some respect 
To the city that blends and mends and tests 
Since 911 we're still livin' 
And lovin' life we've been given 
Ain't nothing gonna take that away from us 
Were lookin' pretty and gritty 'cause in the city we trust 
Dear new york I know a lot has changed 
2 towers down but you're still in the game 
Home to many rejecting know one 
Accepting peoples of all places, wherever they're from 

Brooklyn, bronx, queens and staten 
From the battery to the top of manhattan 
Asian, Middle-Eastern and Latin 
Black, white, new york you make it happen</song>
      <song title="Crawlspace" track="13">There's a party going on in here for real 
I got more product than Ron Popeil 
So deal with that troop were troopers 
The only air time you get is on bloopers 
Beatsie Boys in the place up in the space 
So renovate or evacuate 
You better think twice before you start flossing 
I been in your bathroom often 
Taking punk mc's out I'm all about 
My to do list today is turn the party out 
Getting hot in here no room to breath 
I got my pen in my hand so you best not sleep 
No I'm not Herman Munster or Dr. Spock 
I go by the name of the King Adrock 
So here's a match my ass and your face 
Listen when I tell you dog; 
I'm in your crawl space 

You're in front of my house and you know that's wack 
Bite my rhymes with a scanner from Radio Shack 
You suckers try to front like you've got the force 
But I'll slay like Vader sip you for a first course 
Don't even get me started on intercourse... 
A 14! 9 
Don't step into my zone or even periphery 
Can't grab a hold of my style it's too slippery 
The way you act a fool son you can't erase 
I'll have you running on your way like steeple chase 
You tried to take my title now put it back in place 
But now you're busted wearing panties and lace 
Steeling my style from my trophy case 
But my drive's secure like an army base 
You're sneaking and peeking and trying to give chase 
But you ain't never gonna catch me; 
I'm in your crawl space 

Schematics, blueprints and microfilm 
Calibrate your sonar when I'm in your realm 
'Cause you know we're getting scarier and scarier 
And this extends beyond the Tri-State-Area 
Omnipresent and omnipotent 
My rhymes are whales and yours are rodents 
This means huge compared to very small 
You look a little chilly, can I get you a shall? 
'Cause these rhymes are zoo proof 
They're like anvils lined up on a roof 
Waiting to drop on your corny melon 
'Cause were not buying what you're selling 
First you want to battle then you start to whine 
You're looking hungry, it must be snack time 
So run home where you feel safe 
But don't sleep Cochise; 
I'm in your crawl space</song>
      <song title="The Brouhaha" track="14">Now what the blood clot I rap a lot 
What you gonna do when the beat goes drop? 
Whatcha talkin' 'bout willis? who the illest? 
You know my name's Adam stop callin' me Phyllis 
Ya hear some fuss, you're like what's the clamor? 
It's just me naked on the cover of Glamour 
A phenomenon pandemonium 
The club is blowing up like plutonium 
What's all the fanfare what's the to do 
We're known to bring the hullabaloo 
On stage or at the spa 
Guaranteed we bring the brouhaha 

'Cause it's a brouhaha 
'Cause it's a brouhaha 

There's a commotion that's goin' down 
I talk more shit then drown the clown 
I'm like that freak from Cirque de Soleil 
With my leg behind my head and a rhyme to say 
Ten nine eight seven six five four 
Get upon the mic and I'm a even the score 
one two three, three to two one 
don't carry a knife and I don't carry a gun 
Yo we be making mountains out of Cool Whip 
Pass me the mint for the julep 
Tell me everybody where is the love 
Hey yo what's the motherfuckin' hubbub 

'Cause it's a brouhaha 
'Cause it's a brouhaha 

Communicator check one two one two 
This is bones mccoy on a line to sulu 
Set the bullshit to warp factor one 
Check your tri-corder set your phaser to stun 
Oh mai oui you can catch me 
At jean vie with a pastry 
C'est ci c'est la oh n'est pas 
Qu'est-ce-que c'est le brouhahaha 
Ha haha haha! 
Just back from Japan and ooh I'm laggin' 
Goin' rao rao with the dungeon dragon 
You can dance if you want to leave your friends behind 
But if they don't dance and then they won't dance they can kiss my fuckin' ass 
'Cause it's a brouhaha 
'Cause it's a brouhaha</song>
      <song title="We Got The" track="15">Who got the chance to make things right? 
Why the politicians always want to fight? 
The Christian coalition and the right wing ooooh! 
Let me tell you what you can do 
Step outside the cone of silence 
Too much hatred and violence 
It's time to rewind 
We need a military decline 
Got the power of the mind focused 
Government like a locust 
Are we gone or just going? 
Time to act on what we be knowinh y'all 

Who got the power to make a difference? 
Who got the power to make a change? 
Who got the power to make a difference? 
We got the 
We got the 
We got the 

Eyes on the prize and never wane 
Take the bull by the reins 
If you want it be the change 
Like Ghandi and MLK 
Wait up, got to change the system 
Need knowledge, power and wisdom 
Same way I rock this microphone 
Speak up, just let it be known 
Hey ladies, fellas 
And everyone between 
Take the power back, let them react 
And let's show them what we mean; Check it out 

Who got the power to make a difference? 
Who got the power to make a change? 
Who got the power to make a difference? 
We got the 
We got the 
We got the 

We can work, walk, march and protest 
Think about how we approach this 
Ask questions but they keep frontin' 
Due time we change a little something 
Hey yo don't you know 
Won't forget amaduous diallo 
To the crooked people and the crooked cops 
Got to spread love before the world goes pop 
Never again should we use the A-bomb 
We need an international ban on 
all W.O.M.D.'s gone 
We need a multilateral disarm 

Who got the power to make a difference? 
Who got the power to make a change? 
Who got the power to make a difference? 
We got the 
We got the 
We got the</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Misc" year="9999">
      <song title="In A World Gone Mad" track="">&lt;i&gt;[CHORUS]&lt;/i&gt;
In a world gone mad it's hard to think right
So much violence hate and spite
Murder going on all day and night
Due time we fight the non-violent fight

Mirrors, smokescreens and lies
It's not the politicians but their actions I despise
You and saddam should kick it like back in the day
With the cocaine and Courvoisier
But you build more bombs as you get more bold
As your mid-life crisis war unfolds
All you want to do is take control
Now put that axis of evil bullshit on hold
Citizen rule number 2080
Politicians are shady
So people watch your back 'cause I think they smoke crack
I don't doubt it look at how they act

&lt;i&gt;[CHORUS]&lt;/i&gt;
In a world gone mad it's hard to think right
So much violence hate and spite
Murder going on all day and night
Due time we fight the non-violent fight

First the 'war on terror' now war on iraq
We're reaching a point where we can't turn back
Let's lose the guns and let's lose the bombs
And stop the corporate contributions that their built upon
Well I'll be sleeping on your speeches 'til I start to snore
'Cause I won't carry guns for an oil war
As-Salamu alaikum, wa alaikum assalam
Peace to the Middle East peace to Islam
Now don't get us wrong 'cause we love America
But that's no reason to get hysterica
They're layin' on the syrup thick
We ain't waffles we ain't havin' it

&lt;i&gt;[CHORUS]&lt;/i&gt;
In a world gone mad it's hard to think right
So much violence hate and spite
Murder going on all day and night
Due time we fight the non-violent fight

Now how many people must get killed?
For oil families pockets to get filled?
How many oil families get killed?
Not a damn one so what's the deal?

It's time to lead the way and de-escalate
Lose the weapons of mass destruction and the hate
Say ooh ah what's the White House doin'?
Oh no! say, what in tarnation have they got brewing?!
Well I'm not pro Bush and I'm not pro Saddam
We need these fools to remain calm
George Bush you're looking like Zoolander
Trying to play tough for the camera
What am I on crazy pills? we've got to stop it
Get your hand out my grandma's pocket
We need health care more than going to war
You think it's democracy they're fighting for?

&lt;i&gt;[CHORUS]&lt;/i&gt;
In a world gone mad it's hard to think right
So much violence hate and spite
Murder going on all day and night
Due time we fight the non-violent fight</song>
    </album>
  </artist>
  <artist name="KRS-One">
    <album name="Return of the Boom Bap" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
    <album name="I Got Next" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
    <album name="The Mix Tape" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
  </artist>
  <artist name="Public Enemy">
    <album name="It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Fear of a Black Planet" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
    <album name="Muse Sick-N-Hour Mess Age" year="1900">
      <song title="Filler" track="1">Funky boss get off my back</song>
      <song title="Fuller" track="2">Funky back get off my boss</song>
    </album>
  </artist>
</opt>
